[Music]
Oh, wait.
I bet it wasn't multi-million dollar hacks,
exposed data, or finding somewhere safe to
store
your seed phrase.
Was it?
Maybe it was the idea of decentralizing a
broken financial system?
broken financial system.
Maybe it was imagining a world where people
own their own data and get to sharing the
value
it creates.
Or maybe it was the plan of a broken mind.
Or maybe it was the plan of a fundamentally
better way of connecting, communicating
and transacting. The next phase of the
internet that empowers us instead of
exploiting us.
So why hasn't that happened yet?
Why are we still living with the same broken
system that blockchains promised to fix?
It's because blockchains can't keep a secret.
Enabling open, transparent systems was only
the first half of the challenge.
For blockchains to really change the world,
they also have to be able to protect
our sensitive data when it matters.
And that's why we built Midnight.
To bring down the final barrier to mass
adoption and unlock the full potential of
the decentralized web.
Let's build the internet we deserve. Together.
It's a very complicated step and even includes
Bitcoin Lightning for faster payments.
And with Cake Wallet built in, you can use
crypto in real life through debit cards
or gift cards.
Simple, secure, self-custody. Download Cake
Wallet and take control of your crypto.
[Music]
Good afternoon.
I was about to say good morning.
Sorry.
I was trying to get on here the entire time.
It wasn't happening.
But now I'm here. It's 12.45 p.m.
It is episode 750.
Episode 750.
Sponsored by Midnight. Shout out to Midnight.
Shout out to Midnight.
Guys, go check out Midnight City, man.
Go into Midnight City.
Go check it out.
Let's see. We got people coming. 750, big
deal.
750, big deal, man.
People quit after three episodes. I'm here.
750.
That's official numbers.
Unofficially.
I don't know where we're at, man.
We're higher than that, man.
100%.
100% higher than that. All right.
I'll ask you about your weekends.
I'm sure none of you guys went outside.
Did we eat our own?
What the fuck is going on?
Also, shout out to Polymarket.
Polymarket is the official prediction market
sponsor of the DG brand. There you go.
Also, shout out to Cake Wallet, one of the
most secure wallets out there.
Okay?
If you're looking to go ahead and hold your
Monero, your Litecoin, your Bitcoin, your
Zcash,
go ahead and use Cake Wallet. That's right.
And check out Radar Chat.
Right? The team over at Cake Wallet came out
with Radar Chat.
It is, and also G Markets. Check out G
Markets.
Canada owes us a week.
At least the Northeast.
As somebody who lives in the Northeast, I'd
like to ask for a week back.
Okay? We only get like two months of summer
really here.
And one week was taken away from us by Canada.
Because somebody decided to go ahead and
fucking smoke some trees.
And this is, it's unacceptable.
Okay? We were sitting here.
The goddamn air quality was at a, the index
was at like 600, 700. Okay?
That's messed up.
Absolutely messed up.
Fucked up.
On the show today, we'll have Leonidas from
Dog on Bitcoin coming on.
I think it's Leonidas.
I think it's his third time coming on to the
show.
I didn't tie this right today, man. I'm not
going to untie it now. It is what it is.
I got to, I got to work with this, man.
I got to work with this. What it is.
Come up with a new style, I guess.
Fuck.
Center, bro.
Center.
It's so hard with a camera because it's like,
you're looking at the TV and it's, anyway.
Yeah, Leonidas is coming on.
I think it's his third time coming on to this
show.
So, I need to like come up with, I really need
to come up with like something where
like, nevermind. Anyway, we'll talk about,
again, Dog on Bitcoin. Bitcoin.
I listened to some Bitcoiners cry.
Went into a Bitcoin space and they were crying
about, they were crying about Ordinals and
runes.
And I was like, man, these guys, these guys,
this is why we got a problem.
Also, I held a space.
I came back on space as I held a space.
I will figure out how to integrate this show
and also have spaces run live as well.
But, you know, I don't want to do that because
then like you guys won't show up here.
You guys have a hard time already typing in
the chat.
So, I don't know if I want to do that.
It splits the audience, even though I might
get more of an audience, technically speaking.
I feel like Trump going back and forth.
We'll talk about the World Cup.
Congratulations to Spain. I was rooting for
Argentina.
Congratulations to Spain, though.
Felt horrible for Messi.
I wish, you know, listen, it's been a long
time since somebody did like a, you know,
repeat.
Argentina really played well.
I mean, they did everything in their power,
man.
But Spain got a team, man.
Boy, Spain got a fucking team.
So, congratulations to Spain.
Okay.
Congratulations to Spain. I got Landy in the
back, by the way, in the green room.
We'll bring him on here for 15 to 20 to talk
about the markets and what he sees.
Apparently, I think he's flipped. You know,
this tie is bothering me.
Apparently, he's flipped bullish.
Landy's bullish now.
Apparently.
I don't know. Landy, the puppet, is bullish.
And by the way, Landy is taking my face and
he's putting my goddamn face on...
On puppets and shit, man.
It's fucked up.
It's my IP, bitch.
Anyway.
Anyway, the puppet is wild, man. The puppet...
I think Rob Nelson's mad at me.
After last... I think the show from...
From Friday got a man... Anyway.
I wasn't... Like, was I really on here? I
wasn't...
I wouldn't say I was really on here watching.
Spain had to win. The ritual couldn't work any
other way.
I felt bad for Messi. I got to tell you, man.
Messi's a great player. But, like, you can
see, like...
First of all, they're down a man. They're
like... They're...
How are you going to win in soccer when you're
down a man, bro?
You ain't winning a football game when you're
down a man like that.
It was just like, man... You know, the... That
guy... What was his name? Was it Fernandez?
I think his name is Fernandez.
You know, taking that kind of fucking penalty,
man.
You're already... You know, you're already...
You're already not doing well against Spain.
And then this guy, like, decides, you know,
fuck it. I'm done.
Now, you got fucking 10 men on the fucking
field.
Well... But they could have won.
Actually, they could have tied the game at the
end.
Like, it was that close. Because, like...
They had, like, two or three good chances at
the end. And they just, like... It didn't work
out.
So...
So close, though. So close.
So, so close.
Anyway.
Episode 750.
Sponsored by Midnight. Sponsored by
Polymarket. Sponsored by Cakewall.
We'll look at some of the things on Polymarket
later on here.
Let's bring in the fucking puppet.
If he don't... If he doesn't have energy
today, I'm throwing him off.
Puppet, what's going on?
Get the fuck out of here, bro.
What's it like looking in the mirror there,
David?
What is this shit, bro? What is this shit?
That does not look like me at all.
What the fuck, bro?
This looks exactly like you.
I want to welcome you to, you know, a very,
very belated
welcome to the $DOG Army.
But also, welcome to the puppet army. Yeah.
Very belated. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You've been in the $DOG Army for a while.
You just heard of Dog on Bitcoin. What are we
talking about?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I mean, maybe if you're talking in the mirror
like you are just right now. Hold on.
You're welcoming me into something that I've
been loud about?
Wait, what the fuck are you talking about?
Are you smoking crack today?
I'm sorry.
I'm over here just, you know, enjoying coming
back from being outside for the first time
in a long time.
So, you know.
What is that? That doesn't even look like me,
man.
I can you not see the eyebrows?
This is clearly you.
Look at those eyebrows.
Look at look at look at look at what he's
doing right now.
Those are the eyebrows right there.
You just you know, you're you got some weird
fetish, bro.
It's fucking weird.
Anyway, I looked at.
I still feel like there's bullish sentiment,
though.
Like it looks like every crypto account is
getting taken down.
So, yeah.
By the way, I've looked at the list. I don't
even know any of them.
So I don't know, like if they're prominent
figures in crypto or because I've been around.
I've never seen them.
So I have no clue.
Maybe X is now going completely after.
Is it is X going completely after crypto?
I don't know. I don't know.
It's I've seen a few accounts and some friends
that actually that have mysteriously
disappeared.
Their account suspended.
And I'm not really sure why, to be quite
honest, because I don't think that they were.
Really doing anything that was violating the
term some timeout or timeout.
Hold on.
What? I don't have gray hair on my hair.
I got it right here. I'm right here.
But relax over there. Bits.
OK, just because you just because you're
grayed out doesn't mean I'm joining your club.
OK, not yet.
Not yet. No black hair.
OK, relax yourself.
This over here. This is from crypto.
One hundred percent.
It's all black here.
Black here up until here.
OK, now.
I mean, I got to work.
I can do as many revisions as I want to this.
You know, David, I came out and people like
men, women are saying, yo, you look sexy
with the little salt and pepper.
I'm like, I keep it.
Hey, bits agreed with you. Bits agreed with
you.
Yeah. Look, I I I had to induct David into the
puppet army.
All right. He is now a seven, seven, seven,
seven. Oh, gee.
Opium enjoyer.
Right.
So for those guys, don't get too excited on
tick tock.
I don't know what the fuck he's doing with
this.
Yo, he posted a picture of me as a goddamn
puppet.
It doesn't even look like me.
No, that's the real David. Don't let him fool
you.
This all of this. This live camera view is a
is a deep fake.
He's actually a puppet in real life.
Deep fake. Deep these nuts.
Anyway.
Yeah.
Somebody DM me. They're like, yo, your teeth
are so white.
I'm like, yeah, because I brushed them.
Is that the right reaction? I don't know.
Like, it's just like, yeah.
You're also not like you're not a smoker or
anything.
Nah.
I don't smoke. I don't drink.
Like, I really don't do shit.
Not even not even a little bit.
Not even like a shot.
Wine or champagne or something.
I like I'll drink champagne. But like, I don't
know.
So I'm not going to go to the bar and hang out
at like one of the events and have a shot.
But I can hang. But that's my whole thing,
man. I've always had this argument.
I can hang out without drinking.
Why do I get it? I like to be in control.
Like, I don't like to.
I see motherfuckers like take.
Oh, I'm just going to have a beer.
And then it turns into a fucking.
Disaster.
And I'm always the doesn't make it a driver,
bro.
I'm always driving people home. Like, I don't.
I like to be in control. I don't want to be
that. Oh, you're.
It's like walking out like all fucked up. No,
that's.
But I will say that I.
I do have to like the Eastern European or the
European gene in me.
To where I can take shots and I don't feel
them.
But if I sniff.
A goddamn bottle cap.
In terms of like beer.
A beer bottle kind of thing.
I thought that was going to go a different
direction.
I know where you're going.
But if I. If I smell.
A beer cap.
I'm cooked. I don't know why.
I asked my doctor.
She was like, yo, this is just like.
I don't know.
The yeast affects you like that, man.
I can't. I'm telling you, I drink beer.
What? All I need to do is drink like a little
bit of beer. I'm good.
So Voodoo Ranger basically would knock you
out.
I like Stella.
Stella.
Yeah.
I mean, that's. I don't like Keineken.
I think Keineken tastes like piss.
I liked Corona's.
Like, don't get me wrong. Corona's were cool.
I went to Cancun and there was a contest.
Or who can drink the most Corona's and shit.
Yeah.
I got to the third bottle.
I just fucking passed out.
I was just curious. Cause like, I don't, I
don't actually drink.
I'm a social drinker.
Like I'll have a few drinks out socially or as
you might remember on some late night spaces.
Yo, 100%.
But I'm not into wine.
I'm not into any, like I can, I'm not into, I
don't know. Just never been. You know what it
is?
When you play sports your entire life and
you're strict about like, I don't know.
I've never had a thing for it.
I'm naturally fucked up.
So it's like, what, what, why do I need to get
more fucked up?
Yeah.
I don't drink like to get, uh, if I get it, if
I'm out socially and I, and I catch a little
buzz, it's very infrequent.
Um,
although socially online and then sitting at
home on a space, I realized,
yeah, I'm having a little bit too much.
So I actually stopped that because I was like,
you know what, not going to have a, not going
to have a drink here and talk to people on the
internet because before you know it, you
just keep going.
And then, uh, then you end up as a mess of a
little puppet.
So, but yeah, no, you heard, you heard
somewhere that I was bullish.
I'm not sure where you heard this, but I seen
it on the timeline.
Okay.
No, what I'm doing is I'm laying out the
conditions for, for what I would be looking
for, for further potential upside for Bitcoin.
And, uh, of course, uh, that being a vector
for direction in the rest of the crypto
markets.
And then what those conditions would look
like, um, if they failed and went to the
downside.
Yeah.
So in particular where Bitcoin is right now,
we just closed a weekly where we finally got,
um, a bullish divergence in momentum and in
relative strength.
And in order to see this actually get mean
reversion, because we're in a downtrend,
mean reversion would be price moving back to
the upside.
I'd want to see daily closes above around the
area that Bitcoin is trading now, uh,
in particular around 65, 750 or so for the
weekly.
And then I would be looking for price to try
to push a little bit higher, but I'd want to
see day, uh, daily closes close over close
price momentum start moving to the upside
pretty
soon.
The danger is though, if we do see Bitcoin
fail here and it dropped 62 and a half, then
it
starts to look like it could turn around into
another lower high on the weekly, um, below
61, eight is where that would start to present
itself.
If we start to see daily closes come to, um,
uh, coming into the end of the week where the
weeklies might close below there, that would
open the lows back up and potentially lower
for another leg down.
But right now there's not a lot to do.
Bitcoin is kind of trapped in a pretty tight
range right now, you know, around 62 on closes
to the downside.
There's been some swings below to around 65 to
just above 65 on the upside.
So we need to see Bitcoin breakout and it's
really about, you know, seeing which direction
it takes.
If we do break out above here, you know, I
would be looking for 68 to 70, 70 to 72, and
then 72 to 74. And there's about $2,000 at a
time of resistance overhead.
Yeah. And then of course, if it falls through
the bottom side, there's still the lows and
that's
still an area to be keeping an eye on as
support around, you know, 58 to 60.
Um, but it would increase the chances that we
start to, you know, get another leg down.
If we did see that the big thing here is that
just like in the prior bear market lows, we're
starting to see that bullish divorce, uh,
divergence form on the weekly.
And we need to see multiple drives, whether it
comes from lower low price action, or if
we get a nice rally up and then put in some
equal low, higher low that gets a bullish
divergence.
These are the things that we want to see
develop throughout the summer coming into
fall to actually start setting a macro low
area of interest, whether it's here or lower.
And, and I think that it's important that
people understand the conditions because it's
still a bearish trend on higher term
timeframes.
And until we see that turn around and break,
especially break the downtrend, which is, you
know, on a monthly at 82 and a half, which is
a big, big area.
That's the prior higher low close.
Um, and now a lower high close.
If we start to see that breaking, a lot of
people get really excited, but it's really
about
the next move down to higher, lower, equal low
structure.
If we were to see something like that play out
other than that, you know, it's still a move
in progress to the downside.
So it's all about just setting the, the
conditions that you're going to be looking for
to watch
to see the market structure change and just
prepare.
I've said this a million and one times here,
everybody's sick of it, but here in lower,
it's time to accumulate, especially in this
time period in the markets.
And you've said it many times, sentiment is
shifting.
You're seeing NFT excitement come back.
You're seeing meme, uh, coin, uh, excitement
come back.
This is all right on time for what we've seen
in prior cycles.
And I'm, um, that's actually what gets me
excited because this is the one thing, even
though, you know, we've had some changes in
market structure and when we made a new all
time high prior to the halving and kind of the
muted rally above the prior all time high
and then into a bear market is that we are
seeing people start to come back.
And more importantly, we can actually see
people that we follow again.
So we know that people have been here.
We just couldn't see them.
And the algorithm was really hiding a lot of
people from, from each other here.
No one really left.
And it's really, um, I think encouraging to
see that there's a lot of people still
building
and prepping for the next bull market.
So it was impressing.
I, you know, I don't do spaces.
Yeah. I've officially kind of like for the
last, what, 10, 11 months, whatever it's been
like,
I don't do, I did a few pop-up kind of things
like three, two or three or whatever.
But I did one last, uh, last weekend.
I opened up a space and it got over like 350
people in it with,
it was unannounced.
And it was at, you know, later at night on a
Friday where, you know, I'm thinking some
people went out and obviously spaces are
saturated to begin with.
And it was cool to get on there and just have
a conversation with, you know, a few people
that, you know, I've had conversations with in
the past.
Um, for those who are joining in today, who,
uh, who are coming from, let's say spaces and
you heard me for the first time, welcome.
Cause I do this show from 12 to 2 PM Eastern
standard time from Mondays to Fridays.
I appear on Ron Nelson's Rob Nelson show.
Excuse me.
On Wednesdays at 8 PM Eastern standard time to
talk about politics.
You can catch us on Tik TOK. Also we stream
everywhere.
Um, I just want to say this.
Number one, um, it's what I said on spaces.
I wish everybody the best of luck, you know,
whatever they're doing, whatever project
they're
creating.
Cause I, I had DMS come to me yesterday and I
was just like, I was really like taken back.
I was, uh, I wish, I wish that space was
recorded. It wasn't recorded.
It was an eight hour space.
I believe it was eight hours, right? I think
it went eight hours.
Yeah. It was pretty close.
Yeah. I was just trying to, and for those, you
know, a lot of people who tune in here, tuned
in there, and you've already heard the message
that I pushed out there stating how, you know,
I'd love to be a part of a real movement, you
know, like the second coming of like a wall
street bets type of thing, hopefully, you
know, and I've been preaching this for months,
you
know, on here on the show where, you know, I'd
love to see everybody, you know, come together
and, you know, because if we all did come
together, it'd be fucking fantastic.
Um, but I'm working, I'm working on my own
thing.
I have my own brand that I'm working on this
brand a lot.
I'm working on my own thing and I'm all, I'm
working on my own product.
You got G markets, right? Like I'm working on
things that are, are mine.
Um, and I said that I wish every here, here's
the thing I said, I said, I wish, and this
comes from the DMS that I got.
It's like, I wish everybody the best of luck.
Like, regardless, like whether we speak, we,
we don't speak.
I hope that you fucking win big time, but I'm
not endorsing anything.
I'm like, like what if I'm, if I get into
something great, but like, I'm not endorsing
things unless I really, really, really, really
feel like doing that.
And, um,
and somebody said that I, I said something
about somebody's
shit that I, I fucking shitted on it.
I didn't shit on nobody's thing.
And I know that exact moment because I was on
my headset, which, you know, I have these,
you know, I put on these and, and I couldn't
hear somebody.
And I said, I kind of said, what did you say?
Did you say this?
Cause I thought somebody was joking with me
and then they pronounced it again.
And I said, okay, I wish it the best of luck,
but you know, it's been spun.
And I think people, I think people come on
here thinking that they can bully people.
And, and that's, and I'm going to just say it.
I say things with my chest, man.
I'm going to be here, you know, like I say it
with my chest. You already know this Landy.
At the end of the day, I wish y'all success,
but I don't have to say anything about
anything.
I hope y'all win.
I hope everybody creates something that's
magnificent, but I'm doing my own thing.
That's it.
I think everybody's accustomed to the David
that was dragged nonstop for fucking months,
for fucking months, for no reason.
That David's dead and buried.
He's not here no more.
Okay.
So again, I hope y 'all win whatever I want
to, you see, the thing
with me is I don't talk in the back channels.
I don't have back channels to talk into.
I will tell you if I need to say something, I
will say it to you and I will not give any
fucks about it, but I have nothing to say.
I wish you all the best.
I hope luck's on your side. I hope you win.
But this whole thing about I have to say
something, I don't have to say anything.
I'm building this time.
I'm building my own thing.
That's it.
And I'm talking about products.
I'm like, I'm focused on my own thing.
Like I'm not, that's why I stay, do you
understand why I stay away from spaces?
It's nothing but drama.
I'm not saying all of them, Landy, but I'm
saying a lot of these spaces are just like
every time I open up a space, I do it in good
faith.
I always do spaces in good faith to try to
bring people together.
And then the words are twisted.
And it's just like, it's not worth it.
I'll still continue to do like one, like once
a week, I'll get on the microphone to go ahead
and do something. But otherwise, I'm not, I'm
not even interested.
It's the same thing. It's never changed.
It's literally the same thing. Hasn't changed.
It's unfortunate because you have good spaces,
you know, Wolf Bitcoin and Wolf Financial,
they run great spaces.
See, I can, I can talk about, it's, I don't
view them as competition.
So I can, I can just say like, Hey, I think
they run great spaces.
I think there are one or two over there that
are running great spaces.
I can say these things.
I think we've got caught.
I think motherfuckers are still caught up
three, I think two to three years ago with,
I think, no, for the most part, ever since I
had spaces, I've brung everybody up.
I've tried to give everybody a platform, a
chance to speak to my audience.
It's to my audience that people are speaking
to.
I've worked for this.
I've done this.
I've worked my ass off to be here.
And I've always tipped my cap and I respected
the people that have come along the way.
But I know who those people were and who like,
but at the end of the day was me.
Like I, nobody handed me this stuff.
Nobody, nobody handled zero.
I've contributed as much as people have
contributed.
Do you feel what I'm saying on that one?
Yeah.
So I feel like, again, I needed to address it
because like when I got those DMs and people
are showing it to me, I'm like, bro, this is
why I stay off.
This is why I like being here on my show.
On this show, we talk about crypto politics,
whatever it is, things that are trending.
And I feel like, especially when I have guests
come on, I feel like I'm in total control.
Like I just feel, even if you've got people in
here trying to go ahead and stir up shit,
little Johnny's here today. I've seen him from
the corner of my eye. Little Johnny's here.
I love him. I don't ban him from viewing the
show. I want him to watch. It's more
engagement.
But I'm in control.
You get, you feel me?
Like on spaces, I don't, I think you can be in
control on spaces, but then you have,
you have this thing where, which this is what
I left was.
You have, if somebody doesn't like something,
now they're opening up a space and now they're
taking your words out of context and now it's
all about this.
So they're going to use you as, I'm tired of
being used as a stepping stone.
Like if you guys are really about that life
and you're good with what you're fucking
doing,
you don't need me and you don't need to use me
as a stepping stone.
You don't need to smear my name and drag me
through the fucking ground.
Do your thing.
You know, it's, you know, it's really funny
for somebody who's not that important, which
is, it's constantly directed towards me. I'm
not that important. I got no motion. I got
this.
I don't got anything. Right.
It's funny though, that you motherfuckers will
use my name to go ahead and give yourself
some motion. So make it make sense.
I don't have motion, but you talk about me.
Look, there is about me.
You drag me through the fucking ground.
Then you wonder why, like that part of my
life, that person, that nice person that would
come on to spaces.
That guy is buried.
Like that motherfucker is dead.
Like that DG version is dead.
He's gone.
And I have no feelings.
Well, look, it comes down to a few different
things.
One, you were always very generous with giving
the microphone to, to
relatively unknown folks
and just kind of letting your stage stay open
for conversation.
Right.
And, um, you are on that space.
Like, did I say anything bad about anybody?
Not that I heard. No, I try to tell people
rally with each other, have conversations
with each other, support each other. Okay.
If you want to support each other, you can
support each other. It's okay.
I have not come out here saying, don't do
this. Don't do that. Don't like him. Don't
like her.
Like, I don't, I don't care.
Like that is, that is not, that is not my job.
You guys have two eyes. You got two ears.
You can listen in.
You can see for yourselves whether or not you
want to fuck with people or not.
And if you don't just fucking keep it moving.
Just keep it the fuck moving.
Listen, I just, again, like, I don't mean to
interrupt you Landy, but like, it's just
like, when I seen those DMS was like, I owe
nobody nothing.
Zero.
Nada, not a goddamn thing.
That's the mentality of the space though, is
somebody owes somebody something all the time.
And quite honestly, you know, you've, whenever
you were regularly running spaces, you let
pretty much anybody up and you were very
generous with your platform.
And, you know, I, I think that there are
spaces that, um, you know, there are spaces
that do
that still to this day.
I think that, um, a lot of folks, myself
included, you know, you know, this, uh, the
shows that
I go to, um,
they're, they're curated and focused on a
particular topic with a particular
crew.
Right. And I think that that's, you know,
that's kind of the way that a lot are starting
to
trend these days because realistically, uh,
the audience is tuning
in to, um,
to listen to certain personalities about what
their perspectives are on certain things.
And when it is a show with a format, I think
that it actually, uh, allows for a lot more
control of the stage and what's going on.
And even then, you know, it can, especially
with me on stage, it can definitely go off the
rails, but you know, it's not, it's not even,
it's less about gatekeeping and more about
kind
of the ethos used to be in the very early days
is everybody was getting together.
Spaces were new.
Um, you finally got this, this, you know,
these various platforms, whether it be
clubhouse
or when spaces first launched, where everyone
get together and talk about the stuff that
they love, but then it just turned into, um,
you know, a lot of infighting and a lot of,
um, you know, things that we see today.
There's a space going on just a moment ago and
it's just insults being thrown back and forth.
Um, now of course it's a Bitcoin space, so I'm
not very surprised by that.
Listen, I heard one of these Bitcoin spaces.
It was absolutely horrendous.
Um, we'll talk more about that.
Uh, I'll bring you, you know, you'll be in the
green room, but I'll bring you in if necessary
because I want to, I just want to talk about,
I want to talk about that kind of stuff. Uh,
yeah.
And then I'm, I'm moving forward from it.
So I will never touch on this topic again.
It's done.
So yeah. Y'all can go ahead and have your fun.
Well, I'm excited because I know you got Leo
here.
Yeah. Leo nice is coming on in a minute or
two.
We'll go to a commercial break.
Okay. We'll talk about everything that's
happening.
Talk about door. We'll talk about memes.
Talk about all that good stuff.
Dog mode nodes, baby.
Oh, here we go.
Hell yeah. We'll be right back right after
this.
Puppet.
Goddamn puppet.
Everybody say bye. It's a puppet. He'll be
back though. He's here.
Puppet.
Puppet. We'll be back. Right after.
What first got you excited about blockchains?
Think about it.
I'll wait.
I bet it wasn't multi-million dollar hacks,
exposed data, or finding somewhere safe to
store
your seed phrase.
Was it?
Maybe it was the idea of decentralizing a
broken financial system.
Maybe it was imagining a world where people
own their own data and get to sharing the
value
it creates.
Or maybe it was the promise of a fundamentally
better way of connecting, communicating, and
transacting. The next phase of the internet
that empowers us instead of exploiting us.
So why hasn't that happened yet?
Why are we still living with the same broken
system that blockchains promised to fix?
It's because blockchains can't keep a secret.
Enabling open, transparent systems was only
the first half of the challenge.
For blockchains to really change the world,
they also have to be able to protect our
sensitive
data when it matters.
And that's why we built Midnight.
To bring down the final barrier to mass
adoption and unlock the full potential of
the decentralized web.
Let's build the internet we deserve.
Together.
Ladies and gentlemen, we all know this in
crypto.
Ownership matters.
That's why Cake Wallet.
Cake Wallet gives you full control of your
digital assets.
All in one easy-to-use application.
You can store Bitcoin, Litecoin, Zcash,
Monero, and many more with just one secure
backup.
Swap between coins in seconds.
No copying addresses. No complicated steps.
And even includes Bitcoin Lightning for faster
payments.
And with Cake Wallet built in, you can use
crypto in real life through debit cards or
gift cards.
Simple, secure, self-custody.
Download Cake Wallet and take control of your
crypto.
Welcome back. Welcome back.
You know what? I'm going to purposely get more
sponsorships.
Just so I can have like 19 commercials.
Just the fucking... Yeah.
I'm going to get more sponsorships onto this
show.
Look, I can have like 40 sponsorships here.
You know, I might do that.
Just so we can play like an hour's worth of
commercials.
I know Cake Wallet looks good.
I've been telling you Cake Wallet is...
Never mind.
You guys are... This is what I'm talking
about. You guys don't listen.
You guys don't listen. By the way, anything
that I say here is just educational.
It's not financial advice. Not a financial
advisor.
This is a guy who clicks keys and talks on a
microphone.
And... Into... This thing.
Camera.
Stuff. Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen, we got...
We got this guy Leonidas. He's making this
third opinion on it. Now he's on here.
Leonidas.
What's going on, brother?
Yo. What's good, David? It's great to be back.
Third time, man. Like... That's a big thing. I
just want to let you know. That's a huge
thing.
Look, I love it. Everybody loves when I come
on here. I always...
I always enjoy it.
There's always plenty going on. So...
We never seem to have a shortage of things to
discuss in the Bitcoin ecosystem.
And it's great to be back. I just hope you're
doing well.
And glad to see you're going strong.
Thank you. And same to you. It's... I'm
glad...
I've actually sat back with Popcorn and
observed you whipping ass on the timeline.
And also in spaces.
You want... Let's dive deeper into...
Let's dive deeper into that.
What the fuck is going on with the Bitcoin
Maxi crew over there?
Um... So... Man, yeah.
It's kind of a little bit of a mess right now.
The Bitcoin ecosystem has broken into these
different factions.
And everybody's at war with each other.
So... This is a war at the social layer of
Bitcoin, I will say.
They're trying to take it to the consensus
layer.
But right now, it's purely a social layer
thing. So...
The reality is there's a bunch of people who
care a lot about Bitcoin.
Bitcoin and want to see it succeed and want to
see the price of Bitcoin go up.
They just disagree about how we make that
happen.
And the direction that Bitcoin goes in.
So those people are fighting on X and in X
spaces.
Perpetually, 24-7.
We've been at all times at war with each other
on X right now.
So there's a little bit of...
If you're not in the Bitcoin filter bubble on
X, you might not see this stuff.
But if people are, it's been crazy, man.
There's... Yeah.
There's a few...
There's a few characters on this app that like
to stir the pot, you know, kick the
hornet's nest and just try to create as much
chaos as possible.
And, you know, if you were there during the
block size wars, you remember...
It gets kind of messy when a decentralized
network has to figure out who's the boss
and like what the direction is.
Because there isn't like a very formal way of
doing this.
It's kind of like a mass psyop you have to do
to everyone to convince people that
your side is the future.
So it's very interesting what we're going
through.
Very reminiscent of the block size wars, I
would say.
Maybe a little bit less leadership and less...
A little bit less reason being used.
It's a lot of emotional craziness, man. It's
crazy out there.
Do they not...
I'm looking at some of these people that are
talking about Bitcoin.
And I specifically started looking...
Maybe this is bad, but I look at when their
accounts were created.
And it's like 2023, 2022, 2024.
And they're... Okay, like...
And some people say, well, you can't judge on
that.
But I'm like, yeah, but it's the first time
I'm hearing from them.
And they're telling people how things should
be working.
Do they just not understand this new
generation of Bitcoiners, I guess?
I don't want to call them Bitcoiners because I
think Bitcoiners are more open-minded.
These new generations of maxis, do they just
not understand culture, meme culture?
Like, they don't understand that, like, dog on
Bitcoin will bring
a youthful movement onto Bitcoin who will
ultimately purchase
more Bitcoin as a result.
Yeah, look, it is interesting.
Your observation is an observation that I've
had as well.
I think a lot of these individuals,
specifically who are in this Bitcoin, DOTS,
BIP-110
community, I believe, yeah, they showed up in
the last cycle.
Sort of like post-FTX.
It's been very interesting to have these
debates with them because what I found is,
yeah, they don't seem to understand Bitcoin
very well, right?
I think we have to take a step back and
understand, like, how we got here, right?
So Bitcoin had this major governance battle in
2017.
The side that won ultimately decided to scale
Bitcoin off of Bitcoin with this lightning
network, which is a really cool state channel
solution.
The issue is that it didn't really manifest
itself in the sort of level
of adoption that it needed to be this, like,
huge success, right?
In 2021, they finally built this thing, they
deployed it, and it's supposed to just
overnight, you know, these El Salvador is
going to have these circular economies
with mass adoption of Bitcoin.
And everybody's doing lightning network and
using it to buy coffees and all this stuff.
And it just didn't happen, right? It's a cool
tech.
It's like a novelty for, like, Bitcoin maxis
to mess around with, but it didn't work.
Like, it's just the reality.
Like, we don't have billions of people using
Bitcoin as money. That did not happen.
I think eventually it will happen.
I don't think the lightning network is going
to be how we achieve that.
But the bottom line is the group of people we
anointed, Bitcoin Core, to sort of
run Bitcoin and take us down this path of the
lightning network and scaling off chain.
What that's ultimately resulted in is a failed
experiment.
So we're kind of back to the drawing board.
People are revolting against that group of
people.
And you now have these three new factions.
I call them, like, the suit coiners.
So these are, like, the paper Bitcoin, Wall
Street, ETF, Saylor guys, right?
And they come here and they're, like, very
smart.
They, like, understand economics.
You know, they're coming from Wall Street.
Many of them are already, you know, very
financially successful.
And then you've got the sort of, like,
Ordinals and then runes, meme coins, JPEGs,
the crazy experimenters, DeFi on Bitcoin, the
DGens, okay?
And that's, like, the crypto natives.
Like, imagine your Ethereum DGens and your
Solana DGens.
It's that, but it's, like, an even crazier,
like, hardcore Bitcoin version of that.
So that's us.
And then there's this group of people who
started as a reaction to us.
They're like, whoa, whoa, whoa, pump the
brakes here.
We don't like that there's meme coins and NFTs
on Bitcoin.
So then this group of people, this is the
people who are proposing this 45110.
It's a Bitcoin improvement proposal that tries
to stop Ordinals and NFTs on Bitcoin.
That group of people, I call them, like, the
ossifiers or even more appropriately,
the downgraders. They want to, like, take
Bitcoin backwards.
They don't want any innovation on Bitcoin.
And those three groups of people coming out of
the 2021 cycle, those
three groups of people captured all of the
newcomers.
So the newcomers, it's not very sexy to go be,
like, a follower of Adam Back anymore.
People are, you know, seduced by Luke Dash
Jr., DogCoin, Saylor.
These groups have captured all the newcomers.
And now we're all sort of jockeying for power.
And it's a little bit of a mess, man.
Nobody, it's like nobody really knows what's
going on in Bitcoin anymore.
Like, I have a direction that I think Bitcoin
should go in.
And we're going to fight for that.
We're going to fight like hell for dog mode
and to make sure that Bitcoin stays,
you know, censorship resistant and neutral at
the base layer.
But there's a lot of people who disagree with
that.
And, yeah, we have to fight these guys and
win.
Do you, because you, I'm listening to you, you
brought up something.
Do you think that Bitcoin does lack
leadership?
I mean, who inspires you in Bitcoin?
Like, I don't see somebody who, like, really
inspires me where I'm like, wow, that
person is telling me a future that I can get
really excited about.
Like, I see people selling number go up.
I see people, you know, selling some sort of,
like, thing that's, like, super niche.
And, like, okay, I guess if you're in this,
like, weird anarchy community, maybe
this is, you're into this.
But, like, why are we, like,
why are we not representing ourselves and
telling the story that needs to be told?
Like, if I look around, I live in the U.S.
You know, a $5 footlong is now, like, $15.
The dollar menu disappeared.
Like, a burger is, like, $10 at McDonald's
now.
And I don't know, man.
It's, like, the left in our politics says, you
know, one reason for that.
The right says there's another reason for
that.
Both are totally wrong.
They're both completely lying to everyone.
Cost of living has nothing to do with any of
the stuff that they talk about.
We fundamentally have a system that's broken,
right?
Bitcoin is the solution.
We have a group of people who have, you know,
essentially centralized power over
our money supply. And they print money like
degenerate retards and expect,
you know, everybody to just be okay with that.
And then blame each other when there's, like,
you know, ridiculous levels of inflation.
So, Bitcoin is the obvious answer.
And a finite supply of money, 21 million
Bitcoin.
This is the answer.
I don't really see anybody articulating that
to the American people.
I see a bunch of people kind of fighting with
each other.
So, yeah. I don't know, man. It's weird.
I've gone into spaces.
I've listened for five minutes.
Either they're talking about furniture or
they're, I went in the last space I went into.
Some guy named Puncher.
Maybe I'm wrong.
And he was like, how dare you guys support
Ordinals? And how dare?
Like, we have to pass this.
And the co-host was, like, calmed down because
he was trying to explain the ethos of Bitcoin.
And he was like, you don't denominate it in
Bitcoin.
You're saying it in US dollars.
I'm like, holy shit.
If I'm new to Bitcoin, if I'm just new and I'm
rolling up in a space like this, I'm out.
I'm investing in gold.
Or I'm calling Peter Schiff.
Hey, Peter, what's fucking going on?
I think, you know, I think you have the
opportunity.
So I've said this to Landy, who's backstage,
and I'll let him on for, like, a question or
two.
Because he was like, bring Leonidas on.
Dog mode. Bring it on.
I'm like, okay.
I think you have the potential to bring a
hell of a lot of new people into Bitcoin with
what you're doing.
Like, I really, and I've stated that so many
times.
I'm not just saying that because you're on the
show. You can replay it.
He said, this is exactly what Bitcoin needs.
And this is something that Saylor, who's been
on the show in a lot, don't need to
push this away.
This is necessary.
You want to bring the younger generation, the
more youthful generation, like that
cypherpunk generation, back into this
motherfucker?
This is how you go about it.
So that's how I feel.
Yeah.
So I think Dog's really unique in that it is
this, it's purely designed to create this mass
onboarding event for Bitcoin, right?
Like, if a meme coin on your blockchain goes
to the moon, that's tens of millions
of people downloading self -custody wallets.
They're probably going to end up buying
Bitcoin in order to buy Dog.
I watched this on Ethereum with Shiba Inu,
right?
Like, this is literally the absolute max best
scenario for your chain is
that you get lucky enough to have this meme
coin that just goes insane, right?
There's nothing like it.
Yeah. You got to get people under your chain
somehow.
And you got to get people actually using the
chain.
The problem with Bitcoiners is coming out of
the block size wars because the group
that lost wanted to scale L1 and get people to
use L1.
And they sort of adopted this mentality of the
side that, one, that is bad to use
Bitcoin, which, like, that's the first
mistake.
Like, everything we see today, everybody's
using ETFs and Saylor's MicroStrategy
product instead of actually buying custody and
holding their own keys.
Like, none of these spaces that you're
listening to, David, they don't talk about
educating people how to, you know, custody
their own Bitcoin and, like, not your
keys, not your coins.
They just completely gave up on all that,
right?
And this whole new generation of people that's
here, they don't even remember ever
hearing any of that stuff.
So, like, somebody has to basically sort of do
a reset here and be like, whoa, like,
let's pump the brakes.
It's cool that you guys are trying to get,
like, nation states and institutions to join
Bitcoin.
That can be a way that we make Bitcoin go up.
But it's also important not to just completely
throw out everything that made Bitcoin
incredible and the culture that got us here.
So, we're really the people who are going to
do that, right?
Like, we are the ones who use Bitcoin every
day.
So, a few stats for you here.
Majority of transactions in a Bitcoin block
are Bitcoin meme coins.
Bitcoin meme coins are more popular than the
BTC transfers of money or
store value on the Bitcoin network right now.
Like, we're actually using the chain.
These guys just told each other, hey, guys, we
got to stop using the chain. So, we showed up.
And now we do our DeFi activity.
And that is the number one activity on the
network.
By transactions, we've paid over half a
billion in fees to secure the network.
We're now doing this Bitcoin client called Dog
Mode.
Like, we're the ones actually kind of using
the network.
And when you're the ones using the network,
you kind of get a say in what to do.
Because the miners work for the people who use
the network, not the people who hold,
you know, Bitcoin in some paper wallet that
don't really understand how the network
works or how the governance works.
Welcome to the breakdown.
By the way, you're on episode 750.
That's a big thing.
Okay, hold on. That's a fucking big thing.
Joined by Leonidas.
Guys, I'm sure all you guys have tuned in to
obviously watch.
Watch your boy go ahead and drop knowledge
here for all of us here.
Shout out to TikTok for giving me the limited
band again, unoriginal content.
I just, I give up with them.
Like, every single note that I send in.
Basically, everything that we've designed is
unoriginal, apparently.
Their algorithm is hella stupid.
All right.
You look at the markets.
Memes are a big thing right now.
I'm sure you see it, Leonidas.
Like, memes are a really big thing.
And you have all these chains that are coming
out.
You got Robinhood's chain.
You got, obviously, Base.
Base app has been switched over to Kobe.
How do you feel about the meme economy in
general?
Do you think, do you think it comes roaring
back?
Do you think we'll have, like, a real, real,
with, you know, Robinhood's a behemoth.
So, Robinhood comes in.
They're, they're, I have always said that,
like, they're the best onboarding tool
for normies to come through.
Because a lot of people use it, like, more
than anything else.
But with all, with about four chains right now
or five chains fighting to get meme,
the meme economy's attention.
What do you see for the memes in general?
Yeah, look, I, I think memes are, like, if you
win the memes, you win the internet culture.
You win the crypto natives. You win the
activity.
It gives a reason for developers to go build
more things.
It's sort of the spark that lights the fire.
I think memes are, like, these are the most
important thing that your blockchain
has to be good at.
Which sounds crazy.
It sounds kind of crazy.
Like, oh, you know, meme coins are the most
important thing in crypto.
But if you actually watch the way that these
ecosystems grow up, you start with these
kind of silly memes.
And whether they're pictures of monkeys or
they're, you know, a $DOG coin.
Like, this is how you get people to use your
blockchain and, like, build the decentralized
exchanges and build the lending and, like,
build all this stuff.
So, I think it's, like, this is, like, a
requirement.
Like, if you're building a blockchain and,
like, you don't have any memes, like, good
luck, man.
You know, I'm wishing you luck.
But that's how all the chains that I've kind
of seen that are these, like, multi
-purpose, general -purpose blockchains have
succeeded.
Like, Ethereum and Solana, they won because
they won the memes, right?
And if you get people doing the monkey
pictures and the $DOG coin on your chain, you
win.
So, Ethereum, for some reason, in their
infinite wisdom, decided to, like, you know,
love and embrace the memes for one cycle.
And then, like, tell everyone during the bear
market how bad it was that they're doing
memes.
So, then they did the memes on another chain.
And now that chain is kicking the other
chain's ass.
So, it's like, you want the memes.
Everybody knows this now.
We want to bring the memes to Bitcoin with
Dog, obviously.
You know, Robinhood, Vlad, these guys are very
smart fintech company people.
They're going to try to get the memes.
Coinbase is going to try to get the memes.
It's a battle for the memes.
If you have the layer where everybody's doing
these meme coins and NFTs, like, you're
going to win because you're going to have that
sort of crypto -native degen audience
to provide that initial activity that's needed
to bootstrap your network.
I think long-term, there will be much more
serious use cases you get to build on that
network.
But to start the network, I mean, this is
really the only successful roadmap to starting
your network. It's like winning over the meme
attention economy.
So, I've talked about that.
I'm going to get to that question, but I don't
want to lose this one.
This is what I wanted to ask you as a
follow-up.
So, Dog on Bitcoin has been super successful.
And I'm not, look, I'm not paid, okay?
And that's one thing I love, that, like, this
was super organic.
In my eyes, like, I call for what it is.
I'll say things are bullshit and what.
This is super organic.
The fucking community is fucking amazing.
Amazing.
And, like, I can talk about you guys all day
to get engagement, but I don't do that.
Like, I just, I say once in a while, what's
up?
But I see you guys all talk to a lot of the
community members in the DMs.
Like, yo, like, I think this is really going
to do really well.
And it needs to do well because it will bring
more people into Bitcoin, which is, listen,
I went on to, you know, Leonidas, I went on to
National TV to talk about Dogecoin when
they brought me on there for Bitcoin.
It's like, I was like one of literally the
first people to talk about memes and people
thought I was insane.
But I said, like, Dogecoin brought people into
Bitcoin.
It, like, it really did. That's just a fact.
That's an indisputable fact. Dogecoin was huge
for onboarding people to crypto.
And people were just like, how, I had maxis
come at me from, from Ethereum and from, like,
Bitcoin and Litecoin and shit.
And they're like, how can you do this?
Like, this is not the, I'm like, you
understand you guys don't know how to explain
Bitcoin,
You have Bitcoin, but you don't know how to
explain it.
Somebody comes into a room, you rip them
apart.
Oh, yeah, you motherfuckered me. Let me go get
some Bitcoin.
No, that's not how it works. It doesn't.
And memes, to me, are more relatable.
So if I sit down with somebody and explain
blocks and how a chain works and all this
stuff,
Taproot, Lightning Network, they're not,
they're not trying to hear that.
They're not.
But memes, I could sit down with somebody and,
like, say, and just within two seconds,
they understand.
And then we can have a dialogue.
And then that leads ultimately into Bitcoin.
I wanted to say, I think.
Because they don't understand meme culture,
the Bitcoiners, they don't understand meme
culture, that they're scared of what you're
doing.
They're scared also because they've seen pun
fun respectfully.
They've seen what's happened there. You know,
like, tickers coming out every two seconds.
And I think they believe that'll happen to
Bitcoin when I don't think that would actually
ever happen.
So that's just my take. I could be wrong.
You might say, you know what, Dave, I think
you're wrong.
But I think I'm right where I think, number
one, they're not very well versed on meme
culture
or culture in general. Like you said, they
just came in here.
They graduated last cycle.
The good people retired because they don't
want to deal with the nonsense.
But they don't understand meme culture.
They don't understand the culture at all.
They don't know about the cypherpump culture
to begin with.
And I think they're scared that like if you
succeed, which you will no matter what, dog
on Bitcoin will succeed regardless.
But if that succeeds, that means that there's
a potential that everybody starts using the
network and just you do have utter shit on
pump fun that's coming out.
And I think they might feel that that could
happen to Bitcoin. But what are your thoughts?
So my honest thoughts here are these people
just, yeah, they definitely don't understand
meme coins.
But I think the bigger takeaway is like these
people are kind of irrelevant, David.
They just don't matter.
Yeah. They don't do anything, right?
Like they're not, you know, Bitcoin isn't this
thing where there's like some huge Ethereum
foundation that kind of controls everything,
right?
Like no, there's no boss.
There's no real, nobody's really in charge.
So you can try to tell people that like I run
Bitcoin or I'm in charge, but nobody's in
charge of this chain.
So there's not some huge treasury that like
that group of people gets to determine what
happens.
Like this group of like laser eye maxis, like
they don't do anything.
Like if you actually look at the last 10
years, like these people have done like two
upgrades
to the network for the most tiny, tiny little
minute things that are totally irrelevant.
Like I would say Bitcoin is succeeding purely
because it's such a beautiful creation at the
start, right?
Like this thing is so like Satoshi is the
reason Bitcoin is succeeding because
he just made such a great, such a great
invention.
And it's succeeding in spite of this group of
idiots, you know, parading around, lecturing.
Like I watched this space like three years
ago.
Elon Musk joins an X space. Yeah. Oh my God.
And this guy who, by the way, like this guy
doesn't even understand Bitcoin very well
himself.
He begins to lecture Elon and try to make it
this moment where he's like this intellectual
academic Bitcoin maxi who's going to dunk on
the richest man in the world. Was it Moss?
Because I was in the room.
I don't even, I don't even remember him
because he's not around that much anymore.
I know his PFP.
I can see his face.
He's kind of obnoxious.
You, dude, you probably were there. You were
probably there. I was listening.
The guy, the guy just like, he was trying to
like score points with his like little inner
circle of Bitcoin maxis.
And they're in this endless game of like
trying to virtue signal to each other, like
who's
more extreme and, and who's the most against
meme coins.
So they're like trying to score points against
Elon Musk because he like tweeted about
Dogecoin
a few times. You know what I'm saying?
So it's like these people have lost the plot.
Bitcoin succeeding in spite of their, I don't,
they just don't do anything.
It just doesn't matter. Like I don't, I don't
wake up and think about, oh my God. You know
what?
I'm going to stop you.
You know, you're, I can sense a little bit of
your frustration because you, you know,
Bitcoin.
Like you've been here.
And then when you have these animals that have
just dropped in here trying
to tell motherfuckers
what to do, it's kind of like, who are you?
Like, what the fuck are you about, bro?
Like I, I, I, I kind of get it, Leo.
Yeah. There's this whole industry around
Bitcoin where like people are writing books
and stuff
and that's all fine and good. I like people
need to be educated about Bitcoin.
Like, I think that's all great.
The problem is the people writing the books,
they just like don't understand Bitcoin very
well.
It's like, you're going to write a book about
Bitcoin.
Make sure you understand Bitcoin decently well
first.
So it's, it's, I don't know, man.
It's a, it's just a weird situation.
I'm not too worried about what they think at
the end of the day.
Like, I just don't think they hold very much
power.
They're not.
Bitcoin just. They don't even have nodes.
Like, it's like. Yeah.
I mean, like it's.
Right. Like, I don't need to win over this
group of people, to be honest with you.
It's like, you're much better off bringing in
a new group of people who isn't like
brainwashed
with this insane ideology.
So that's, that's the plan.
Do, do you see.
So, I mean, have people have the old school
Bitcoiners reached out to you? Like an Adam
back.
Are these people reaching out to you and
saying like, you know what?
This actually is a good thing for Bitcoin.
It puts more eyes, more youthful eyes onto the
network.
Because everybody. You know, here's the thing.
Here's the fucking thing that I don't like.
You contradict yourself. Not you.
They do.
When you say you can build everything on
Bitcoin. You don't need everything.
You don't need these things over here.
You can build. We can build everything on
Bitcoin.
I've been in these conversations.
You can build everything on Bitcoin.
So the moment somebody tries to build
something on Bitcoin, we can't build that on
Bitcoin.
So which one is it?
Can't.
Then you can't dog these other projects. I
mean, these are the protocols.
If you say you can build on Bitcoin anything
you want, we can build it on Bitcoin.
We can make Bitcoin everything.
But then as soon as somebody goes ahead and
creates something and you try to push
it out, then what the fuck, bro?
But it has like an Adam back and a bunch of
the old school cats reached out to you
and said, you know what? We see what you're
doing. We like it.
So there's definitely been some of that.
I would say most of these guys, though, fit
into this camp of they do understand Bitcoin.
They're very bright.
They don't have any sort of like technical
educational limitation in these conversations.
Like they know exactly what's going on.
So there's no way they side with this BIF 110
group of people.
So that's good. They're not like taking the
side of BIF 110.
We're in like a temporary alliance with this
group of like the intellectual maxis
purely because we have a common enemy.
The problem is, though, they're trying to walk
the spine line of being anti -meme
coin, but also anti -BIP-110.
So like the BIF to stop the meme coins,
they're against.
But they also claim to, you know, not like the
meme coins.
So, of course, that's total, total, you know,
bullshit, right?
Like Adam Back has a company that created a
few years ago and it was like a cool thing.
You know, an NFT marketplace on Bitcoin and
all this stuff.
Like the guy is completely intellectually
dishonest in these conversations.
And he's I get what he's doing. He's being a
politician.
He has to basically walk the spine line so
that he keeps his audience.
And he wants to sort of have his cake and eat
it, too.
And like have the Ordinals and runes people
kind of support him and then also have
Luke Dash Jr.'s fans, you know, support him
when that fails.
So he's just trying to be relevant desperately
in a time where, like I said, like
he was in the sort of ruling faction of
Bitcoin for many years.
He was sort of given free reign with
Blockstream and Bitcoin Core to like do, you
know, do this lightning network experiment.
Try to do that future for Bitcoin.
Bitcoin Core to like do Bitcoin and he failed.
So now he's sort of getting overthrown.
And I don't think, you know, he's just he's
just hanging on for dear life to not
just completely be totally irrelevant.
He like he still wants people to listen to
him.
So he thinks the way to do that is to like not
really pick a side.
But the reality is like you got it.
You got to pick a side like we're either going
to do Silicon Valley style, you know,
DeFi and experimentation and have a thousand
companies come and build and innovate
on Bitcoin, which Adam Backstrom totally
before.
He's basically one of those companies or we're
going to be this ossification.
You know, nobody touch anything.
Actually, maybe we will touch something, but
we're going to make the box sizes smaller
and we're going to go back 15 years like that
group of people can win.
And I think we're a much better version of
Bitcoin.
I think people should be building on Bitcoin.
I think it's ridiculous to scare away
developers.
It's leading to a brain drain.
And yeah, Adam Back.
I don't I don't even think Adam Back knows
what he's doing anymore.
Like he he's just kind of going with the flow.
These JPEGers showed up.
These crazy BIP-110 people showed up.
And now he has to like tweet about us instead
of whatever the hell he's tweeting
about three or four years ago.
So he's trying to stay relevant, man. It's a
game of attention.
That is a I'm going to bring in Landy, who I
think is like he's a secret Bitcoin Maxie,
though.
He tries to like I think I think what you just
said about Adam Back.
I think Landy tries to do it.
I don't know if you know Landy, but Landy, we
have, you know, we have Leo on here.
You said, you know, it would be really cool to
bring on Leonidas.
Well, I've run him on.
Yeah, because he's one of the most coherent in
making
any argument about what's happening on Bitcoin
at this particular time.
And has been for quite a long time now since
he's joined the Bitcoin network.
And see, here's the difference between Leo and
a bunch of these other folks that
are out there talking about it.
He's actually worked on the network.
He's actually done things on the network.
He's actually pushed the network forward in a
meaningful way.
Which is honestly one of the reasons why Luke
and the BIP-110 crew is losing their minds.
The biggest thing here is I listen to a lot of
these conversations as well.
And obviously, I've talked to Leo. How are you
doing, Leo?
The biggest thing is there's a lot of people
that have very strong opinions about
where consensus should go.
That have not participated in driving
consensus outside of the social
conversation around it.
Most that I've heard speak on these subjects
have never run nodes.
Don't mind.
And have never supported the network.
And, you know, maybe they're getting into it.
Maybe they will get into it. And I hope that
they do.
But there is this world that they seem
to live in that is unrealistic about what the
Bitcoin network is.
They have a lot of misconceptions about what
it is and how to achieve consensus.
And there's a lot of problems in their own
pushback against
Ordinals and rules.
The solution that they're providing is not a
solution at all.
The limits that are put in place are easily
bypassed.
And they've also gone through and done some
things that I think are and
can be perceived as an attack on the network.
Like lowering the consensus to 55%.
Right.
That is a little odd.
It shows that they don't feel like they have
the support and they're trying to subvert
at this point. And that's actually some of the
key technical stuff.
On the technical side, there is very few of
them that can actually have a technical
conversation. They pop up every once in a
while in the conversation.
But it's typically on the timeline.
It's not usually in spaces or on shows.
Leo can have the technical conversation.
He can have the social conversation.
Much better than just about anybody in this
space.
And the interesting part is he's not wholly
unique in this regard.
But you want to know where the people who
understand the network the most are coming
from?
They're literally coming from the faction that
Leo is representing.
Right. And I think that Leo
said something the other day that I thought
was really, really important.
We were on a stage together with J-Dog in the
Dog Millionaire show.
Shout out to J-Dog.
And Leo said something that I thought was
really important.
And that is that this will be studied.
And I'm of the opinion that this bit will
fail.
It's going to, in my opinion, face plant in
terms of its failure.
This is nothing like the previous block wars.
This is nothing even close to approaching the
uncertainty, the fear,
any of the tangible network level
considerations
that we had to deal with at that time.
And this will be studied.
This will be studied in terms of how not to do
things when you are trying to push
something forward in terms of a proposal.
That will be adopted as consensus.
And as somebody who is a minor, who does
support the network, I
can tell you I've had conversations with many
of my peers in the industry.
And most weren't even paying attention to this
because it was just noise until
fairly recently.
Where they've said, look, we're going to make
a decision
internally in our pools to either support or
not support.
And we're going to let everybody just figure
it out.
You saw probably the leaked.
Well, it's not really leaked, but not an
official announcement out of Foundry.
But Foundry saying, look, if we got 51
% of the pool signals, then sure, then we'll
signal as a pool.
And these are conversations that are happening
across many different pools and many
different miners.
But the reality is, any kind of conversations
with people who are actually doing
this, because this is a business.
At the end of the day, if you are mining at
any type of scale, it's a business.
Well, I want to ask you about the mining part
real quick to cut in.
Doesn't Doug on Moon and Ornals and whatever,
doesn't it benefit the miners?
Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, look.
So then why would you want to push?
Why would you want to push this away?
It means that you have a lack of
understanding.
Well, because they're not making an economic
argument.
The folks who want this off of the network
aren't making an economic argument.
They try to make an economic argument, but
it's a very weak one.
About the load on the nodes.
And then it just drifts into spam and straw
man arguments.
And realistically,
you know, we had just an hour ago, we had one,
two, three, four, five blocks,
zero SAT per V byte fees.
We literally had 0.43 SAT per V byte on the
network.
We are not filling blocks up.
And even the current block right now, one SAT
per V byte.
Most of those transactions, as Leo had
mentioned earlier, they're up returns.
This is people moving meme coins around.
This is the economic activity that's happening
on chain.
And, you know, miners really liked what
Ordinals
and runes brought because it was a boon.
While we're getting emissions coming down,
we're getting this fee generation that's going
up.
And a lot of the pushback to Ordinals and then
later to runes when
runes activated at the halving on 420, which
went a brilliant halving date.
But, you know, was that we're going to have
saturation on the network.
Fees are going to remain unrealistic and no
one's going to be able to move transactions
around.
It's going to clog the network.
Nobody's going to get all of the quote unquote
economic activity that they say, you
know, in terms of transfers of Bitcoin,
monetary use of Bitcoin, they claimed wasn't
going to happen.
And they don't even want to recognize that
this is monetary use of Bitcoin because
they don't want to.
They see just the pure network level of, oh,
somebody paid a thousand dollars at
the time in Bitcoin for 246 sat picture.
Right. Because they don't want to see the
economic layer that was happening there
and that there is that's a that's a transfer
of real Bitcoin.
That is economic activity. You might not agree
with that economic activity or you
might not value that particular trade of
Bitcoin for, you know, the thousand
dollars in Bitcoin for the 246 sat.
You might not value that, but somebody did and
they valued it enough to make an economic
transfer on the network.
So it's economic activity. And right now the
miners were economically motivated.
Yes. And the last question I want to ask Leo
is about dog and obviously.
Anything, any new updates, what can you tell
us?
Any new stuff in the works that we don't know
about that the audience doesn't know about?
I'd love to go ahead and hear it, by the way.
Shout out to the $DOG Army.
You guys are fucking crazy.
OK, the fuck out of my DMs nicely, I politely
say.
But Leo, what do you got cooking up there?
What do you guys got cooking up on with dog?
Yeah. Next six months, six or 12.
Listen, we've been fighting these guys for
years.
This is not a new thing.
From the moment there was an ordinal
inscription hitting the network,
Luke's been very angry and trying to stir up
people against us.
So we've been fighting these guys for years.
We've gotten tired of essentially a group of
people who kind of sit around all day
and try to lecture other people and tell them
what to do in the block space that
they bought and are doing valid Bitcoin
transactions in.
If you buy the block space, no other
blockchain does this, by the way. No one gives
a shit.
It's like you buy the block space, you do your
whatever you want, your meme coins,
your NFTs, your D5, and you move on with your
life.
You validly purchased it from a miner. Like,
do whatever you want.
These guys want to sit here like call monitors
and like slap everyone on the wrist.
And we just got tired of it.
We're like, this is ridiculous.
The stuff they're actually arguing about, by
the way, it's all these relay policies,
which are these sort of made up kind of fake
rules is what I'll call them for now.
So dog mode strips out two of those fake
rules.
And we're going to be able to do transactions
on Bitcoin that we traditionally have
been doing, but we've been having to go around
the Bitcoin network directly to miners.
So instead of Bitcoin core relaying our
transactions, we're just creating this like
black market for Bitcoin transactions where
I'll go to Mara or Ref2 and have them
mine something for me. That's not ideal.
That's an unhealthy state of the Bitcoin
network where you have sort of a group of
insiders who has special relationships with
miners who can do these transactions,
but nobody else can. That's not great.
So these nonstandard transactions, these sort
of four megas, you've seen these like
huge images get put on Bitcoin, this sort of a
thing.
We want everybody to be able to have access to
do them.
There's a huge demand to do them.
And we're basically creating a Bitcoin client
to compete with Bitcoin core to compete
with Bitcoin knots.
And this is going to, instead of going in the
Bitcoin knots direction of restricting
everything, we're going to actually open it
up.
We're going to open the network up to what is
possible and specifically starting
with these two very specific changes, which is
removing the dust limit down to one
sat and basically allowing people to make up
to 3 .9 megabyte transactions on the network.
And there's a lot of demand for these two
things.
There's a lot of economic incentives for
people to run a node and make those
transactions.
And we don't have to fork the network.
So unlike Bit110 that Landy correctly pointed
out is going to fail. I mean, it's already
failed.
Let's be honest. Like this thing has already
It's not going to happen.
Unlike that, like all we have to do is
basically make a few tweaks to fork Bitcoin
core, make a few tweaks, and then get people
running these nodes and broadcasting,
you know, economically relevant transactions
into a mempool that incentivizes, you know,
at first a little bit of hash rate, but then a
growing amount of hash rate to mine
those transactions, right?
And if you're a miner and you just see these
juicy transactions sitting there with
a bunch of fees attached, the incentive is
you're going to mine them probably, right?
So we've done this actually before.
We just didn't make a Bitcoin client to do it.
This is how we lowered the kind of floor on
the fee market from 1 sat to 0.1 sat.
Um, opera chart has been increased as well
through a similar sort of means.
So we're just going to keep pushing the
envelope here and I'm measuring Bitcoin.
Winning on Bitcoin does not mean, oh, I dunked
on someone in the next space.
Nobody remembers that. Nobody cares.
Winning on Bitcoin is when I run Bitcoin a
hundred years from now and I look back in the
blocks,
Bitcoin blockchain is just a bunch of these
four megabyte blocks.
Did you leave your, like your legacy is left
in those blocks.
If you're not in those blocks, you did not
matter.
Doesn't matter.
Nobody cares.
The $DOG Army is leaving our stamp on this
network inside of the actual blocks.
And you're going to see that you've seen it
for the past couple of years.
And we're going to now do it as even more, uh,
kind of higher governance level in the
network.
And you're going to see the legacy that we
left on this network.
And the $DOG Army is, uh, we're going to, you
know, kind of teach a lesson for if you do
want to make changes to Bitcoin, how to do
that.
A lot of people talk about making changes to
Bitcoin.
A lot of people do all these like crazy things
that'll never work.
We're taking the sort of easiest, shortest,
least path of resistance way to making these
two changes on the network, upgrading the
network and showing people that, Hey, you
know, the $DOG Army is here to stay.
We're part of this. We're the ones actually
using the chain.
We use BTC as money every single day.
We're securing the network and paying the
fees.
Now we're the ones actually going out and
doing work to onboard people.
You know, we have a say here.
So this is us, uh, this is us firmly planting
our flag on Bitcoin.
Well, I want to give you, uh, let me go ahead.
I've told you this before. I think you're
doing a phenomenal job.
Uh, I, I've absolutely fuck with dog on moon,
uh, a dog on big Bitcoin, excuse me.
And, uh, and I think the $DOG Army is, is one
of, one of the most special communities in,
in our space. Like they show up every single
day.
Like you're on the show today.
So there's more of them on here, but like they
do show up to this show. I see them out there.
If I ask a question, they pop up.
I love seeing that.
So, uh, I really do hope you win.
Absolutely huge.
Uh, and, and definitely, you know, it's not
just, but dog, you're fighting for bigger
things
here with what you're doing.
So it's really cool to see.
So I do definitely appreciate you.
I appreciate it guys.
Landy, David, this has been great.
Appreciate you guys.
Have you on in a few months from now.
Landy.
Shout out to Landy also. Thank you, Leonidas.
That's Leonidas, man.
The leader of the, the leader of, I would say
the leader of, uh, yo, he, he's leading more
than there's just, uh, just more than just
dog.
I would, I would say more than the $DOG Army at
this point.
Look, it would, I think a lot of people, you
know, a lot of people don't pay attention
to Bitcoin.
Hold on. Let me go to a commercial.
We'll be right back to assess this situation
right after this Landy.
Don't put my, don't put me as a puppet on
this.
Oh, you're going to be a puppet when we come
back.
What first got you excited about blockchains?
Think about it.
Oh, wait.
I bet it wasn't multimillion dollar hacks,
exposed data, or finding somewhere safe to
store your seed phrase.
Was it?
Maybe it was the idea of decentralizing a
broken financial system.
Maybe it was imagining a world where people
own their own data and get to sharing the
value
it creates.
Or maybe it was the promise of a fundamentally
better way of connecting, communicating, and
transacting. The next phase of the internet
that empowers us instead of exploiting us.
So why hasn't that happened yet?
Why are we still living with the same broken
system that blockchains promised to fix?
It's because blockchains can't keep a secret.
Enabling open, transparent systems was only
the first half of the challenge.
For blockchains to really change the world,
they also have to be able to protect our
sensitive
data when it matters.
And that's why we build Midnight.
To bring down the final barrier to mass
adoption and unlock the full potential of
the decentralized web.
Let's build the internet we deserve.
Together.
Ladies and gentlemen, we all know this in
crypto.
Ownership matters.
That's why Cake Wallet.
Cake Wallet gives you full control of your
digital assets.
All in one easy to use application.
You can store Bitcoin, Litecoin, Zcash,
Monero, and many more with just one secure
backup.
Swap between coins in seconds.
No copying addresses. No complicated steps.
And even includes Bitcoin Lightning for faster
payments.
And with Cake Wallet built in, you can use
crypto in real life through debit cards or
gift cards.
Simple, secure, self-custody.
Download Cake Wallet and take control of your
crypto.
[Music]
you're muted
I'm muted of course
welcome back to episode 750
sponsored by midnight
check us out Fridays we're going to do
midnight city obviously
check us out on midnight city
also shout out to Polymark the official
prediction market sponsor of
the breakdown also
cake wallet secure wallet
secure wallet for litecoin Monero bitcoin and
zcash go ahead and get it
and also look into
not a sponsor but radar chat
look into radar chat
especially for you bitcoiners
go look into radar chat
this week we're definitely doing memes
we're doing memes I'm going to focus on memes
I want to bring on the memes
and some of the best communities
within the memes to talk about the memes and
the culture
I really want to go ahead and do that
100%
because I think a lot of protocols are
dropping the ball
they don't understand meme culture
they can care less about meme culture
until it's too late okay
y'all might have the greatest products in the
world
but you got nobody on your chain okay we're
here
memers it's okay to be a memer
you meme every day of your life it's so it's
perfectly fine
I say this I say this all the time life is a
meme
anyway what'd you get out of the conversation
had with Leonidas today look I love Leo I
think that
you know I talked to Leo
recently when when Leo and
and in the $DOG Army crew the runes and the
Runestone crew came through to Bitcoin and Leo
really started to get involved
in the Bitcoin ecosystem as any Bitcoiner I
was skeptical
but I was also
already tinkering with the Ordinals protocol
on my on my minors
and on my nodes both personally and
on the business side of things
and this is this is where
I kind of hung back and I watched and I waited
and I listened to the conversation and I
talked to people building in the space and Leo
and
the crew that he was and is rolling with
really what I what I learned was he understood
Bitcoin at a core
technical level he understood Bitcoin
and he had a really good argument and really
good arguments for why he wanted to do
what he wanted to do to push the limits of
Bitcoin on the chain while remaining
within consensus and
he won me over very quickly
with how intelligent he is
with his understanding of Bitcoin with his
understanding of crypto in general and his
ability
to bring people together
to build something towards a much wider vision
so I have a ton of respect for Leo I think
that he's he's going to
likely be one of the
he's already a pretty controversial figure
in
to the maxis right
but I think that he's going to help lead the
movement
because the social layer of the movement needs
a leader and I think that what he's already
done
and what he's going to continue to do is lead
that movement forward that is going to
progress
Bitcoin and the understanding of Bitcoin not
just at a not just from hey this is easier
to onboard people to Bitcoin but I think that
what he's doing is going to help push Bitcoin
forward in terms of understanding Bitcoin's
ethos from a technical level as well because
even those folks who got involved in Ordinals
and runes and then of course in the dog
army over there
many of them started out just like hey I want
to get some Bitcoin I want to get involved in
this
there's some meme coins over here and now they
actually understand in a lot of these guys
you don't know their names they're not hugely
popular they don't have massive accounts
some of them do
but they actually understand Bitcoin from a
technical level and they're out there at
events
they're out there in the real world onboarding
people utilizing dog
utilizing
that as it is an introduction to Bitcoin and
self custody and I feel like they
really played a big role even at the time in
non-custodial Bitcoin because most
people were trending in the direction of
having their Bitcoin on an exchange and not
working
with wallet and not your keys not your coin
it's like that ethos right
post-block wars coming into 2021
and then through the bear market in 22 a lot
of it was like you know we had those few
shocks
but as soon as the market started to turn
around everybody forgot like oh yeah I gotta
go get
my Bitcoin and they're all on exchanges again
they're trading in and out they're not
exploring the wallets and the innovations
that are happening with Bitcoin
and realistically
I think that he's a great representative for
Bitcoin
and not just the $DOG Army but for Bitcoin
itself and I think that he's helped to educate
a lot
of people and there's others like him that are
doing this but I think that he is
one of the voices that I have seen rise to the
top
and will continue to ascend
and look listen the community is great they're
very passionate they don't
okay you know there's a community that shills
like they don't they don't just
they break down what dog is so that's really
cool to see it's like they're not just
shilling you
they're breaking it down and they're telling
you why
and I and that's a reflection I think on
leadership
I really do believe because you've seen
communities just like hey buy this buy this
they're not even they're not even
most of the time they're not even talking
about buying they're just like this is why
and I've had conversations with people
within the dog community
they're really cool they're absolutely fucking
cool to go ahead and have a conversation with
by the way shout out to Johnny
yes I you know I don't I don't get that
respect but yes 750
official
750 750
episodes
of the breakdown 750
that's the official that's the the unofficial
who the fuck knows
but
in terms of you need a Leonidas you need
people that are
that are willing to to change the fucking
attitude in Bitcoin you know how I've stressed
this
I've stressed this so many times to you and
you don't have to agree either you don't you
see
the thing is that it benefit look I asked you
that question does this benefit the miners
right
it does absolutely yeah so then you've been
looking for incentive I've heard
this a lot we're looking to incentivize the
miners we need to incentivize the miners well
here
you go
oh we can't do this though then
the contrary the way they contradict
themselves consistently listen again the
graduates of last
cycle but they're contradicting they don't
even know shit they don't know culture or this
culture
this is why I say what I say that's it and by
the way whoever captures and I'll say this
whoever
captures the meme economy will win
bottom line
yep can you imagine like if you're a bitcoiner
and you're talking about bitcoin going to
a million and especially the chat that I
caught for like 10 minutes it was at night
with this
guy plumber or fight what was his fucking name
this guy came in was just like
his his fucking profile was created in 2023
and he's talking about denominations and
bitcoin
and all this stuff he's like anti runes and
Ordinals all this shit I'm like
and then and he's we're supposed to use this
as as money
how are you going to get this message out
there if you do these kind of things like who
think this all starts with
well look I have never
let me let me
put this out there because I know that there's
a few people who I guess have had
have expressed to me that they've had bad
interactions with this gentleman
I've never had a bad interaction with puncher
I think that he's very passionate
I haven't listened to these conversations you
gotta listen I was in that room
you know I don't shit on nobody
this man was in the room saying
respectfully he was saying
we shouldn't be calling people names and then
he was calling people names
I understand you don't agree I've heard this
before I have never experienced it myself
I've had pretty robust conversations with him
and others he was wiling out
I get his passion for bitcoin if you know him
the passion for bitcoin congratulations I
don't
know him I know of him I'm just saying if you
know of him the passion is great but to not
open up your ears to a different opinion is
crazy I might not agree
but you can just allow the person to speak
look
that's one reasons why I think a lot of these
spaces
Leo and I talked about this a little bit with
J-Dog and Vincent
and it's crypto revolution
so shout out to those guys and a few others as
well and I'm sorry if I'm missing your names
but
one of the big things is I think that this is
actually all going to be healthy for bitcoin
at
the end right but I also believe that many of
conversations especially when you go into some
of
spaces you're getting a lot of and I mentioned
this when I posted I reposted
sailors 110 reasons not to adopt this
basically or 110 counterpoints or whatever it
was
a lot of people what you're about bit bit 110
right so he he put out a post the other day
and look he's utilizing bitcoin in a way that
I'm not
personally I'm not of it it's not that I'm not
a fan of it you can do whatever you want I'm
not
it's not for me right and that's the thing
that I think that people
misunderstand and you know Leo brought up the
lightning network and stuff like that
lightning
network is something that I chose not to
participate in right because I felt that
layer one needs to be the focus and like I
have a lot of views that maybe differentiate
myself
from folks like Leo and Udi and all these
other guys that are on the ordinal side and
even
in the $DOG Army I have a lot of different
viewpoints of what I think
bitcoin should be right and how to go about
getting to the end road
of getting to adoption but then there is okay
I'm not going to sit here and
dog on others
for how they're going to use if it's falling
within the consensus model everything in
Ordinals
and in runes falls within consensus model I
actually support I own Ordinals I
support the Ordinals protocol I own runes I
own dog on bitcoin thank you a
bunch airdropped and of
bought more
because
I love that pushing
the edges and the edge cases as far as you
possibly go
move
fast and break things and if it still remains
within rails consensus great I'm all
for it is there
downsides to it there's always pros and cons
to anything
and I think that's healthy what think is
unhealthy about what's happening right now
that will
result in a much healthier robust conversation
as move forward is that the unhealthy
portion is the manufacturing of consent
socially for this particular bit when there
is no network support behind it and there can
arguments about like well no there's
15% of nodes or blah
okay yeah you guys can go and you can rent a
bunch of nodes and a bunch of you know you can
go
to the data centers or you can go to your
start nines and whatever and you can stand up
a
bunch of nodes that support it sure
great
so can anybody else that's running any other
version
of of
of bitcoins
core
right or dog or anything anybody can stand up
nodes and guess what if it's economically if
miners are
looking at this from the economic side things
and nodes start to overwhelm the network
they'll just stand up a bunch more of their
own like what like they got the money you
don't like
what are you talking about like this is when
it comes down to it it's
it's it's what is economically viable on the
network
and
you know I am of the opinion that this will
result in better things for bitcoin in the
long run
like the fact that leo is going out and
challenging core was something like dog mode
this is something that you want to see whether
you agree with it or disagree with it if you
disagree with it you know how you vote you
stand up nodes you run miners and you put your
money
where your mouth is right like the fact in the
matter is there's a lot people that talk a
game
in this game that don't
money where mouth is when it comes to
the that want make a name themselves it's
politician right
that's coming
to the network and they want to a name
themselves and they feel this is the hill to
die on it's
mom donna make a bunch promises you can't keep
and you hope elected right
and so
this is
model and want back
quick the this is and I 100% agree with the
insightful comment
that Leo made to me the other day and that's
that this will be studied for how not to do
things
because we need examples of that a lot things
in this space will be studied for not how to
things I know right there's a whole lot of
case studies for how not to do things
when he didn't embrace the economy
like that studied Solana will be studied for
how embraced meme economy and took mind share
away from
Ethereum which first market with memes
and they
gathered this audience which allowed them
ahead and showcase it to institutions to
have institutional players built on it
and look I really think at the of the day
this will force those who don't
want if they come the side this you a lot
flip right when this doesn't go through the
that envision a lot
flip and just rely on spaces for 12 months
they'll about it 12 months yeah they're
about it and here's the thing
that
many
also flip
side like nothing ever happened like never
they never even this is this will literally be
a blip of bit on
! and one
the core things that will do is it will allow
for those to study and like look
this is a case study for how we need move
forward and solve realistic
problems that we do face
future you no one here and you I've big critic
of the quantum fears
right but no one here is stupid enough to say
that quantum won't someday be a threat
and but know what but
what when think about now
nobody's talking about quantum computing or of
course because what's his name put up a
freaking
how many what was it like a million dollars or
whatever it was for bullshit that could do
wasn't
a good case study 15 bytes but like nobody's
about
but I'm saying I'm saying it's not it you I'm
saying you shouldn't look into it
because
is something that needs to be solved these
real actionable problems it's not that wasn't
issue
the issue was this forced urgency it's just
like BIP 110 stuff this forced urgency we have
now
bitcoin fails it's a bunch !
let's focused and
once this is over in August
once the mandatory signaling period
is enforced
we are going to then
after that period we're
down business and actually start focusing on
things that matter and do think that it's
going be
gentlemen like Neonitis and people in the dog
army and Ordinals communities and the runes
communities I think that
this
has emboldened a lot folks and a lot BIP1
tenors don't understand this emboldened a lot
folks
who actually have real connections in the
industry who actually are miners who actually
do
run economically viable
nodes which look that's a whole debate in and
itself but realistically this awakened them
fact of like look this and I'm tell you
internally
like I'm talking guys who
pushing
you know near the majority of hash rate on the
freaking network okay I might play like a
small
little puppet here and like an asshole
sometimes or joke around joking
but realistically I've had conversations with
some of these guys and they really do look
this
and go
you this
I perceive as an attack in particular with 55%
stuff
right and anybody who attacks the $DOG Army is
attacking me
you heard and puppet it is attack
on bitcoin the real bitcoiners and we will not
take it
i'm i am i am being serious when i say that
i'm being serious are you trying to say i'm
not
serious right i know you're being 100% serious
i'm fucking serious right now
an attack on the dojo army is an attack on god
i'm sorry there's no dojo army
excuse me $DOG Army the $DOG Army
an attack on a $DOG Army is an attack on me and
the puppet
look i've i've seen puppet
i by the i just want to let you guys know i've
never seen his face he's never
nope and he's had the opportunity to do so but
declined um because he knows that he'll have
black vans parked out in front of his house in
no time
i'm starting to take you seriously on that
shit bro like
did you see the one the other day yeah yeah
don't worry about it
you know that we can actually uh these days we
have the technology that um
if you if you look at the van at one point it
might be black
and then you'll come back out and you'll look
and be like when did the where did now it's
a white van yeah just don't worry about it
you know
just to end it though i just want to say
that let me give him a round kiss
you know
i just want you guys to see
how big i am into memes
if i showed you the emails and who i could
have brought on here today for episode 750
some of you guys would say i'm crazy
but y'all said the same thing when i went on
tv and i talked about memes i wanted to talk
about
the memes and i specifically wanted to landy
was in my ear we gotta get leonidas on
yep
gotta get leonidas on
at one point i blocked
not leonidas landy
because he kept on assing the same thing
i was like fuck this blocked
i brought leonidas on here because i think
that it is important that dog on bitcoin
succeeds
because it will be another on-ramping
situation for bitcoin which is necessary
from all angles
it's necessary to get that new audience of a
breath of fresh air that
people will be able to understand why bitcoin
is so important
and then miners there's always been
conversations well how
can we go ahead and incentivize miners well
here you go
it's beneficial for the ecosystem and
especially when people talk about well more
people need to use bitcoin
there is no argument
now the only thing that i did say is i think
maybe but i don't even think they think this
far ahead or this
i don't even think they even think outside the
box like this but some could see pump fun and
what they're doing and say holy shit this
could happen
if we allow
doggone bitcoin to succeed
Ordinals and rules this could happen to us
so that's the only thing that i'm going to
give them the benefit of the doubt
where they might see that going on and saying
we don't want that here but i also don't think
they understand how anything works and it's
more so of a talking point for them to get
engagement and solidify themselves as being a
bitcoin maxi
and i'm orange pilled check me out
that that's the way i look at this situation
because if you're a normal person who wants
your network to succeed if you're up to me
if you're a bitcoin maxi and you're watching
this you're like this is good because we're
getting new blood in
and when we try to do this we were
unsuccessful
that's just my point of view i could be wrong
and i'm fine with being wrong this is my
opinion it's my take
leonitis
and anybody who fucks around Ordinals and
ruins it's a good thing for bitcoin it's not a
bad
thing it's not a virus it doesn't bring down
bitcoin it won't stop bitcoin from going to a
million dollars per coin it's not going to
stop institutions from collecting it buying
into
it it's not going to stop
and may
from buying an etl it's not going to stop
anything from happening i don't i don't
believe
that to be the case
no and and all of the fear and fud that
surrounded all of it
starting back in 2023 the launch of the
Ordinals protocol look that most that are just
now
becoming aware of bit 110
they haven't even been around or weren't even
paying attention to the Ordinals protocol
launch
right
they
this has been going on for three years you
know we've been talking about more than three
years
we've been talking about this
we've been
seeing it play out on the network side of
things and all of the fears and all of the
straw man
arguments that are thrown out there have not
come to fruition
right there's the CSAM argument no one can
prove that that is even on bitcoin and even
if it was there are other ways that it could
get on there even with an implementation
of bit 110 as consensus
right so there's no these aren't solving the
problems that they claim that they want to
solve
and that they're perpetuating out there as for
the longest time it was all about fees fees
fees
and it makes it economically unsuitable for
people to utilize the network
it just wasn't true it was never true
and
it's a game of economics when it comes to
mining and standing up nodes and supporting
the network right it costs money these are and
from a mining side
most people that are doing this as hobbyists
sure maybe they're getting some sats here and
there
maybe they're just supporting the network
great I encourage that I want to see more of
that
but from
the
large-scale mining side of things including
off-grid miners which is the sector that I'm
off-grid mining is continuing to grow it's a
business at the end of the day it's a business
and it's a choice by the way it's a highly
competitive hyper competitive
environment where the margins are very thin
and you have a protocol that was launched
that stays within the guardrails of consensus
on the network and that has been adopted by
many
and if not all of the large mining pools in
fact all of the large mining pools have
adopted
ordinal's protocol
and they see it as being an economic driver
and at the end of the day if it remains within
consensus and it is an economic driver that is
where miners are going to go and this
is something that I think this will pass we
will see the conversation continue to be had
about it
once this is all done and over with meaning
this too shall pass not that the BIP-110 is
going to
be successful because it's it's not look
everybody's making arguments about no
everybody's just going to signal at the last
minute no
they're not and they're not and and what
they're now banking their hopes on is this pie
in
the sky dream of foundry
going 51% and supporting and then forcing the
other major mining pools to do it I'm sorry
you're
literally pinning your hopes
on something that is a an extremely
extremely
low likelihood in fact this is how you know
and I've said this before this is how you know
that confidence is not very high ocean is not
enforcing
BIP-110 they're making it a choice they'll
support miners running it but they're not
making it mandatory on their pool so this this
is going to be over with fairly soon and
fairly
quickly but the conversation will not go away
but you know what's going to happen myself
others
like Leo and many others in this industry are
going to start pushing this conversation
forward to solve the problems that we know
need to be solved in the coming years to
protect the
network to allow for it to grow and to
continue to onboard people to Bitcoin and that
is
going to happen that is the reality of the
situation and for those living in an alternate
reality they might just find themselves stuck
in that alternate reality and in the end
what's
often going to happen like it has in the past
is they'll probably abandon Bitcoin then come
back later and you know what
it's going to take some time for them to heal
especially those who have built their
personality around this it's going to take
some time for them to heal from this one
because
this is going to be a devastating loss for
them because they've really really put
themselves out
there and they have very very little on chain
support and that
that dichotomy is something that we have not
seen before where there's this mass movement
on
social media where people are pinning their
hopes and dreams to something that is not and
their reputations to something that is not
going to be
something that's going to come to fruition and
it's going to take them time to rebuild
from that and I hope they do and I hope they
can come back and have healthy conversation
they don't have to abandon their ideals to
have healthy conversation they don't know
what healthy conversation is they haven't
you know what it is when you're trying so
desperately to fit in there is no healthy
conversation they're trying to make it's kind
of like what Leonidas alluded to when I
remember
who it was when Elon came on space and it was
Mark Moss and he tried to go
ahead and dunk on Elon which was the stupidest
shit in the world you don't try to
dunk on Elon you try to bring Elon into the
mix you try to tell you
want this way this way Elon fucks with
Dogecoin do you understand where I'm coming
from
yeah because you have a community
that's embracing or or wants him to embrace
and
they're not spewing just like they're not
coming off toxic yet in that conversation it's
kind of I'm dunking on you and then the it's
the same thing they did with Mark Cuban they
come back post game
wrap-up look what I did look what I did I
sunned him
no you hurt in my eyes you hurt Bitcoin by
doing that you
didn't not that Bitcoin won't go again not
that Bitcoin won't go to a million I'm just
saying you could have
brought on Elon you could have had Elon be a
big advocate you
could have had Bitcoin
Bitcoin actually on
X if you would have talked to if you
would have talked to
Elon the right way
right because there are people within Bitcoin
that know how
to talk right if you would have had somebody
have the conversation
with with with Elon
and and broke it down
to them or articulated
it correctly non-toxic
behavior who knows what he would have done
maybe
maybe he does integrate
Bitcoin into X and that's a win for
Bitcoin but you push them away he Elon
remembers that you
know who Elon is Elon
remembers every single
thing done to him I
well I'm gonna say this
and maybe this is a
little bold of me but I
think that X money will
have a crypto wallet
component to it that it
will allow you to have a Bitcoin wallet that's
fine but you wanted
Elon to be on your
side yeah you don't you don't you're
dunking on Elon makes you look like a
fucking idiot because
it probably I believe
because if you look at Elon's history if
somebody does him dirty right what
happens oh yeah go
look at Elon's track
record the minute that you talk you say
anything negative about him or you try to
embarrass him he is
coming for your throat
ask Sam Altman like I
I'll name you a list
so I'm just saying if
Bitcoin's so great there's a way to explain it
listen I fuck with the
toxic maxis because they
serve the purpose to
they stood on business and
they didn't let anybody
fuck with Bitcoin so I
fuck with that also but there's a time and
place to put down your
fucking weapons and
understand the situation
so anyway welcome to
the breakdown we've been
on I don't want to hear
us I don't want to hear nobody say we're not
talking about Bitcoin
this is very important for
Bitcoin and I obviously
I don't think real the
the BIP shit I don't think people are really
taking it seriously it's just a talking point
for
engagement so you know what I think was
serious
what you know what I
think is gonna happen I
think what I think that
they will a lot of
nothing in that regard for
the BIP-110 but what I think is going to end
up
happening is actually the
filter crews worst nightmare
nightmare and that is once
the dog mode is released
and can be run on nodes
and starts running on
miners and there's it
because it'll start with we're already
starting to
see it with some of the pools starting to get
rolling yeah and there's going to be pool
support
I can almost guarantee that
that look if there's anyone
that can gather support for
some something it's Leo and
whoever he's talking to
because he managed to work
with miners to get the
rune stones through to get
the dog airdrop through to
do all of this like he did
something so impressive now
granted he even said that's not how you want
to do it
that's not healthy I don't
want to have to go directly
to miners to do this kind of
stuff because it's end
arounding you know the in
order to you got to do what you got to do at
the end
of the day but I think
that the solution for having
another piece of software to
run that is within consensus
on the network I think it's
going to shock a lot of these
folks how quickly it gets
picked up I think that that
is going to be something that
an unintended consequence that
they did not expect is that
there's always a reprisal to
what you're trying to do and
Bitcoin is famous for that
there's always somebody
working on something else and
and I think that it's going to
end up being very successful and
it may just shock them and it
might just be the shock to the
system that we need in Bitcoin
to get things rolling especially
on chain and filling blocks
again because it's a it's it's a
freaking desert out here we
finally got a two sat per v
byte block in the last 10
minutes this has been it's
been a it's been kind of a
slog let me put it that way
it's been a slog look most of
the transactional volume is a
lot of these larger players just
moving money around but they're
not moving it around every block
right there you know we need to
see blocks getting filled again we
need to see activity on the
network start to increase we need
to see more people getting
onboarded and I think that
between stuff like what Seth is
doing and what Cake Wallet and
the team over there built with
and granted it's on lightning
which by the way I've been very
transparent I was not a
supporter of but it gets people
involved it's good for onboarding
you send them some sats they're
like cool I got my wallet let me
get my keys I'm on this network I
can go to layer one I can do this
right it's a good intro and so is
dog and so is Ordinals and I think
it's gonna end up being over again
I have to do the giveaway we'll do
it this week we'll do a giveaway
for anybody who has Cake Wallet if
you show a screenshot I want to do a
thread on this where you drop you
show a screenshot and then I'm sure I
can use some sort of fucking
mechanism I think I'll use Grok to
select a winner and or winners
depends where you know we'll send
something to your Cake Wallet so
there you go we'll do that and also I
want to touch on two more things
before we go obviously it is 2 49 p.m.
on the East Coast we're two hours 14
minutes in we had Leonidas on from the
dog on Bitcoin community shout out to
him for coming on on episode 750 the
sponsor is midnight shout out to
midnight the midnight network go check
out also midnight city it's a it's a
cool thing to go ahead and experience
they came out a commercial I think it
was dope I saw it poly market is the
official prediction market sponsor we're
gonna get to poly market right now I
have something up because I see that
Rubio is climbing so I wanted to touch
on that for a few seconds here cake
wallet is also besides poly market being
an official prediction market sponsor of
see how I say that fast of the
breakdown you also have cake wallet as
well and you can hold your litecoin
bitcoin your uh like coin bitcoin
monero zcash on it you also Landy was
alluding to radar chat and also check
that out the team went ahead the team
from cake wallet graded radar chat uh
and that is strictly not saying anybody
can't use it but obviously it's focused on
Bitcoiners so shout out to that also I
didn't look at my wallet today so let's
go ahead and look and see what we where we're
at
um where the fuck is sir dg dg okay the
memes by the way disgusting again I'm
looking at the whole followers 359
followers man what the fuck are we doing
what is happening bro what is happening Landy
I don't know but I'm gonna I'm gonna
outpace you everybody uh at this point
yeah I don't know what I gotta do I
maybe I gotta get butt net butt naked and
stuff I don't know
I get butt naked let's see what's going on
here
let's bring Landy and into the mix all
right there goes Landy all right this is
the age of the wallet 23 days I made the
wallet to just buy some Solana memes and
see if I can go and not see but prove to
people that I can I can really get into memes
that pop
okay okay
all right I'm a little bit lost right now
I see one two three we have three white
bulls now oh boy
okay
oh boy look at this yep so we see uh
all right so we got the white bull we got
we got two white bulls the three white bulls
now
um hmm
wow I'm stumped
all right uh one has
one one's at uh 635 the other one's at 201
I haven't called anything by the way just
to let everybody know I have not called
anything uh I have not endorsed anything
um I did I did throw
I'm stumped right now and okay
one has uh it seems like okay
I I need to hold on I need to gather myself
bro
but this is my wallet there you go this is my
wallet
and again at the end of the day uh Landy first
of all
let me start here man let me let me
let me gain control of myself once more here
359 followers what the fuck
three this is a yo Landy it has to be
impossible that like
like I'm not trying to shit on anybody but
like
how do people have like fucking 10,000
even five 10,000 like how do people have that
I don't know man
but 359 like can we get to like a thousand
like I'm not even going to ask for 10 or 20
um
yeah we'll look at this tomorrow man
let me let me look at this actually you know
and then we'll look at this tomorrow so
um
that fucking dog thing makes me laugh I'm not
gonna lie
um but yeah I did buy troll
so I'm not buying anything today but I did buy
troll I did buy bobo
I what else did I buy troll bobo
landy are you here
I'm here
I don't remember what you bought to be honest
uh
troll
bobo
what the fuck else did I buy
look at them
look at them right away you will once you
endorse again
oh Trump thank you Todd I bought Trump so
Trump bobo
troll I know I bought something else pengu
pengu there you go
there you go so four
and during this week I'll buy some more
and and stuff like that so
so there you go that's the wallet
you can go ahead and follow it
shout out to everybody you know
shout out to everybody who uh
by the way who joins in on this show
I gotta give much respect to everybody who
comes on to the show I appreciate you guys a
lot
uh I see things out there on the timeline in
terms of like when I when I when I look
fucking this guy again this fucking puppet
when I look at the
I just want to let you guys know
when I see the timeline
when I'm going through the timeline and I'm if
you
if you feel like I haven't liked your stuff
there might be a reason why
it's not because it might not be good it's
just that
a lot of you guys are putting tickers in your
in your replies
and I can't like your reply
because then that means that I'm endorsing
or somebody will use it as I've endorsed
something
or if I've blessed something or like and
that's why
I won't answer you at times so
if you feel like I'm sunning you
meaning like I'm fading you in any sort of way
I'm really not I see you
I just can't acknowledge you if you're putting
something into the post
on a like like on a random post where I'm
saying hey good morning
somebody hits me with a meme
with a ticker in it I can't reply to you
so just know that it's not me avoiding you
I just can't reply to you
at least not for now
okay I keep it 100
also
let me go through this real quick with the
with the political end of stuff
I got polymarket up right here polymarket
again
the official prediction market sponsor
of the breakdown let's bring this up
of course this is a little pop-up
I knew that shit was coming out of nowhere
Republican presidential nominee 2028 we got JD
Vance he's down
14% but he's at 42%
Rubio's climbing 21%
according to polymarket up 21% to 28% did you
see his his speech
his speech on the 16th I didn't see it so that
is that is that why
Rubio's pumping like this yes it was really
really good
I would encourage you to go go it was the
his speech at the resurgence
of political terrorism conference for the
State Department
I didn't see the whole thing
probably seen clips yeah probably seen clips
it was actually a really good speech
so I mean with this right now
with the way this stands here
I don't know
like here are your two heavy hitters right
these are your heavy hitters
I respectfully say this this is not me
oh he's a Republican he's saying this
I don't see how anybody's beating these two if
they if they run if they run together as a
ticket
I just don't see
I really even if even
it's like what I said last week
you bring in Shapiro or whoever like you just
I don't see anybody beating this ticket the
Democrats need
the AOC's not gonna win it so it's like the
Democrats really need their Obama
and they don't have that right now
they don't have their Obama in that party
that party's fucked up
respectfully speaking
the party's in shambles right now
because they have you know this this idea of a
party coming in the DSA right
they're coming in with this mindset which the
Democrats don't agree with so that
there is fighting there's a huge
fracture within that party
I don't see that in
the Republican Party you have the number
Trumpers and stuff like that
but it's not as big by the way shout out to
the Polymarket for that
but it's not it's not as big as what's going
on
on that side of the fence
so
and
yeah that's it and to touch on spaces one last
time for those who enjoy spaces I enjoy spaces
I will do one once a week I'm not gonna run it
for six to eight hours that was crazy
that was absolutely I woke up the next day
I felt like I had a concussion
I really did I woke up fucked up just like
holy shit man
you missed your workout it was already
yeah it fucks up my day
it fucks up my workout so
no more than two hours okay
no more than two hours
will the show go on
I want to clear make it very very very clear
I ain't trying to take anybody's spot cause I
know
everybody got this spot
I ain't trying to take your spot I ain't
trying to take your show god bless you all
guys
I hope you fucking kill it
anybody who's able to show up daily
to get on a microphone on a camera on a space
and
have a conversation god bless you man it is a
tough and difficult job you gotta have you
gotta have something to talk about you have to
have
it's just you have to have flow you gotta be
the ultimate emcee so shout out to
anybody who's doing it day in day out
if I don't if by the way if you don't hear
from the horse's mouth if I don't come out
here on the timeline and make a statement
it never happened bottom line
respectfully
this year and and this is one of the reasons
and I'm gonna repeat this again one of the
main
reasons I stepped away from spaces was I felt
my energy drained completely and I needed
to go ahead and start taking my brand and my
product seriously and that's what I've been
doing
building out my products
okay g markets and all that stuff building
this stuff out
gochstein.com is coming like all this all
these things that's what I'm that's where I'm
focused
that is where I am absolutely focused
so
if I'm going to ever endorse something
if I'm ever going to really call something
it's going to be something of mine
it's not going to be something of somebody
else's and it's not a shot and I understand
why people take this as a it's not a shot it's
not to downplay anybody it's not to belittle
anybody okay
stop making up these narratives
I'm focused on myself and I'm allowed to be a
little bit selfish and I will continue
to be a little bit selfish towards me because
I've always been unselfish
now it's time for me to be a little bit
selfish and build out the shit that I like
that's really it that doesn't mean that I'm a
bad guy
okay doesn't mean that I'm a bad guy and I
only care about myself
sometimes you do need to care about yourself
I built this shit by myself
respectfully this is not dogging anybody but
I've put my face
I've eaten crayons out here like Landy I put
my face out here
I've built
through the bull through the bear
y'all gotta put some respect to my name and
you don't want to that's fine but this is what
I'll
leave you with it's funny when people say I
got no motion I don't know what all these
things
and then you talk about me so the name holds
weight
the weight the weight on the name there it is
there's weight there
and you you don't have to use it to go ahead
and like
you don't have to
I've never dunked on anybody to go to the next
level in my life and I will continue to walk
that same path I don't need to go ahead and
put anybody down in order to go ahead and
continue
to move up
bottom line
yep you can do the same thing you don't need
to use me as a stepping stool
okay at some point people will be like yo why
y'all motherfuckers talking about this guy so
much
if he's not that good why do you keep talking
about him
people people that there are smart people here
they're gonna tune out
I would encourage you to focus on your thing
and that's it I have only I've only been
supportive and said yo god bless even if I
don't talk to people god bless them I hope
they
kill it
your issues with me
you can take that up with god that has nothing
to do with me your opinions your issue it has
nothing to do with me
zero as you elevate in life people are just
not gonna like you and that's fine and that
is perfectly fine I've seen every every single
builder out here and I'm not putting myself on
a
pedestal with like the greatest builders of
all time but every single builder any single
entrepreneur who has built anything that's
worth shit
every single anytime they elevate the source
come out and people start coming it is
what it is and once you understand that as an
entrepreneur you're gonna
you're just gonna continue forward on your
mission to go ahead and be
absolutely just fucking great and and I and I
hope the same for everybody else anybody who's
building out here who's taking it seriously
who's building communities and all that good
stuff good for you I hope y'all continue to do
this I hope you continue to win but I don't
need
to do anything
I'm not required to do anything if I talk
about something like the door community I talk
about the door community because I know they
truly appreciate me
they've been fucking let me tell you something
about the door community they've been
literally
hollering at me
which feels like years and they haven't been
pushy about it either just like hey
this is what we're doing I think you would
love looking into this it's a conversation and
there's an appreciation there's other
communities that you know I
fuck with also and they fuck with me and I am
okay
with them speaking about it so that
that's my approach
that's it and people are not gonna like it and
that's too bad I didn't like the things that
were
done to me either
so that it is what it is and I'm not gonna
even go into it because I don't
need to but I just wanted to clear the air
today and I
will never you will never hear me speak
about this ever ever and give time to
this ever ever again but you know what
sometimes it is good to come out here and say
like a lot of these things that
you're seeing are not real there is zero
zero way to them
I'm a builder I'm building it's my time
and besides that I hope everybody else wins if
your intentions are good
and if it benefits this space God bless you
fucking continue to go
yeah no no hate or ill will towards anybody I
don't have I don't have fucking hate I
really do not have hate in my heart like I
don't have
hate in my heart I don't wish anybody
bad that's a bad way
to live life I don't
I'm not going to I don't wake up in the
morning stressed out thinking about like I
don't I say I don't
care and not that I just like I just
don't it's not a part of my energy I need my
energy to be focused on
building that's
it that's all I want to focus on building a
great
show helping helping my guys build out
their shows that's it getting guests on
bringing value
getting on calls
that's all I care about educating as much as I
can whatever value I can bring that's
all I care about so thank you for hearing me
out
today because this won't happen ever again I
promise
but I just felt like I needed to do it
I felt like I needed to do it I
ignored I ignore all the fud like I ignore all
the slander all the
defamation all this shit I ignore all this
fucking shit
but sometimes it's just like hey I
let me address this real quick because that
didn't happen
so and we don't have to do this this is what I
talked about this industry likes to
eat itself we don't have to do that
like I see people building over here and
they're doing media too and I'm like yo I'm
congratulations congratulations because I know
how hard it is to build out media good for
you man I hope you win like there's nothing
more I can say good job hope you win we don't
even have to talk to be from good job hope you
win man like
congratulations I hope your project
is successful I said I hope your
project yours right there you mine watching
this if you're watching this
I want your project to be successful
talking about my project I don't know I'm here
to sabotage what
I literally by the way you know it's funny and
this is this is what's interesting about the
space eating itself
and I'll kind of
I kind of have to say this there's
there's a contingent
of people who think that this this puppet is
I've
been accused of being here and a part of your
brand and your network to
sabotage you that is the wildest thing that I
have ever heard and I think it's funny
that if you're going to approach me with that
and accuse me of that what is the base
case like what am I mean obviously I
am like what is the dog the
the insult dog I can't remember his name
anymore I'm
basically like that right but David and I have
really good conversations
lots of jokes and lots of fun but we have
really good conversations about important
topics that
are happening within the crypto industry
within the
political sphere and
about sometimes just society in general
the the notion that you have to to accuse
people of something in
this space in order to elevate yourself like
what David was just saying is ridiculous and
realistically I know from personal
conversations with David he wants to see
people succeed
no matter who you are whether you love him or
hate him and it's the same with me I
want to see you succeed I want to see your
project and the on this program right now
have I ever wish bad on anybody honestly
have I like really told you that I
want I want to see people fail no of
course not because you don't want that
I'm legit like have I contacted I I'm praying
for the down like no oh
yeah triumph the insult comic dog
yeah that's basically
me the insult comic puppet look I don't I I
wish no
one ill will and I if you know what I'll say
also for Landy because since he won't say it
there you know it I love the fact and this is
what you guys
all have to get when you're building
something you got to get somebody who
when I don't want to say I don't lose
focus up that much
overall but you you get somebody who
says yo the bigger picture we're building and
when you have somebody
like that and especially when their intentions
are good because they don't want to see you
dragged or anything and they want to see
you win that these are the type of people you
want to set yourself
yeah Landy will I'm telling you right now
Landy will never go diving deep into
bullshit he's just
like we're building
and that my friend I respect about you
you fucking puppet
I appreciate you and
look that's have to
have that mentality I
really I really do want to see not only you
succeed I want to succeed here this is a
different path for me I'm obviously a puppet
you're doing it as a little
sidekick like Andy Richter yeah you know I'm
just I'm
here because I want to educate people
about where things are going in the space
whether it be
price action or have
robust conversation
about things and to have fun right whether
it's political topics whether it's crypto
topics whether it's Bitcoin or not
Bitcoin I'm here to
have fun entertain
and have good conversations with people and
see my
friends win right specifically my friends but
that
doesn't mean that my
friends win at the expense of others
and in fact that's something that I don't like
and there's a lot of
people here who want to win at the expense of
others and that's not something that I
think is good and when I see it I call it out
but I call it out and we move on and I
don't think that it's I don't think that
anyone here should want to see
anybody fail because we're moving forward
as an industry and if you want to be along for
the ride
you don't want to see others failing
and it's just you know you want to pick them
up like I'm going to say what I'm talking
about like somebody accused me of saying
or calling something
an STD when when I was on space and I
literally I have these headphones
okay these are the
headphones you put on when you go on spaces
when you have
your roadcaster and
somebody mentioned something and I said and I
said STD because I didn't I thought
that's what the person said and then I asked
to clarify multiple times and if the
recording was there then you guys were if you
guys were there then you heard what I said
but if the recording was there I wish it was
there then I can go ahead and say look I'm
like I didn't say none of this bullshit the
fuck what are you talking about I was so happy
to
be back on spaces and the vibe was like so
fucking cool that I was just like like I'm I'm
just
ready to chop it up what are we doing like
how's that like I'm trying to get the pulse of
the
crowd how the memes and talk about certain
topics about the
crypto ecosystem I don't have time for these
like fucking games and look there was
legitimately good conversation happening on
your stage and that's something that
as of late has been few and far between
and that's what I'm saying like it doesn't
make me want to like I'm going to do I'm
going to do more spaces regardless but then
the day like
that's one of the things that could
like it pushes people
away just like man you can't even say
anything like even when the person
even when a person is just like I don't hear
like it's live it's you know like you're not
on
commercial break
it's live some people have it's just a shitty
connection coming
through bro you're trying to fucking hear it
out and I talk out loud I'm the type of person
who talks out loud
period I'm on this
show there ain't no fucking script here like
I'm talking out loud I'm telling you how I
feel at
the very fucking moment sometimes three hours
four
hours later like I'll say shit about ethereum
I'm like man I feel bad but that's the truth
at
the very moment when I say something about
Vitalik smelling or trying to smell
robotic ass that's that's real talk
how I how I see Tom Lee as a bearish signal
that's real talk
Vitalik you better get on here me and fucking
Landy were arguing about this I said Tom Lee
called in
2017 Bitcoin going
here and Landy was like oh nah man I ain't I
ain't going there with it and now I'm just
like I'm
the one who's saying like yo Tom Lee him
buying this shit is crazy because it keeps
going down
well I mean I'm of the opinion Tom Lee made a
mistake when he switched to
ethereum but that's a wider conversation this
is what it is man listen yeah that's a lot of
money they should have put into Bitcoin but
like people like oh sailors buying Bitcoin Tom
Lee's
buying ethereum why doesn't it go up bro
they're not going to fucking finance to spot
yeah like I that's what I'm saying a lot
of the education is
lacking they actually think people yeah
Saylor is like you
got a strategy where can you please open up
the coinbase account let's buy some spot here
look there's a lot
of misconceptions about this industry and
there's a lot of misconceptions about
how I mean that there was people
trying to equate the
short on float of micro strategy stock to the
reason why Bitcoin was going down like
no that's not it
yeah so yeah there's a lot of misconceptions
that are pitched out there as fact and that's
one of the
reasons why the puppet
is ever present on
shows like your show and on the network
and in spaces because
I do not believe
that I think that a
lot of the education
piece where people who because there's a lot
of people who come here to really
actually learn something
about what's happening
whether it be right now
in the moment or how
something works and there's not a lot of
people that actually
are out there discussing
those topics I have a
very niche audience for
that yeah right I'm not
I'm not the the hype up kale well you
know here's the next play guy I'm the
here's what's going on with price action
here's what's going on
with different things on
the network and also
here's a heavy dose of politics that you're
going to either love or
hate and that's you know what I've built
here and for a very
specific reason because I want to be a voice
for
those that are actually
looking for some some
substantial educational value and how to
evaluate certain things
in this market because
we lost a lot of that
and unfortunately we did
it to ourselves because
we promoted a lot of personalities in
particular last cycle we promoted a lot of
personalities that used
to pitch themselves as
educational that were
really just you know
floating out educational
material to then pitch you something to dump
on your head and that
was really destructive and
I think that after
evaluating that towards
the end of 21 into 22
I was like you know what I'm just going to
take a different path
instead of fighting them
and and going to battle
and going to war against
them I'm just going to
consistently put out
content that someone
will find value in even
if that's a small subset
of people and that's
fine right I I come
here I hang with you
we talk about all all these different subjects
and we have a lot of
fun right and then you give me the space to
actually talk facts to people and you know we
see it in the comments
oh this is boring and
you know what you've said boring makes money
and that's a lot of
things a lot of the
problem in this space is
that boring does make
money you know it was really it was really
boring to go to school
at times right yeah I'm
just saying I'm gonna give you that analogy
guys it was boring to go to school but if you
actually finish school
you're sitting most of you guys are sitting in
a really good position you're able to
articulate yourself you have a good vocabulary
probably have a good
job hopefully you know
like these things happen when you educate
yourself on boring
things yeah I don't I don't the only thing
that was exciting in school if you you
really want to look at
it was lunch because you got to go ahead and
hang out and then
recess and gym if you
think about it yeah so
going into class I don't think you were
excited to
take regions and midterm
all this shit like you
weren't excited to listen
to your teacher or
professor talk for an
hour okay well maybe I
was well I was too I
was a geek I might be a I was a geek I might
be a
nerd yeah yeah I was
excited the school like I
was I was on the chess
team I was in key club
oh wow you really were a nerd holy crap
wow I'm telling you I
was I was really in like
I was in these things
like because like I found them interesting
because I I felt like it
would you know when
you're surrounded I had a
moment in school I
remember this was a my freshman year of middle
school my assistant
principal the the 8 p.m. the dean took me to
the
side because I I was
wilding out no doubt
about it 100% they took me to the side and
they
said I had like three bad tests I didn't even
do them honestly I didn't
even look at them they took me into the office
ago I'll never forget
this my AP said you have
two choices one you can
end up a loser and you're
on the right path or two
you can grab the potential
you have and be great
yep and he goes I'm disappointed at you
because
like you're you're smart you
got light to you and this is the route that
you're going
you're not taking anything seriously so you
know
what you're absolutely
100% at this point you're going to be the
greatest
loser and like and I remember and I will never
forget that speech I'll
never forget that 20
minutes of being like
literally I want to say he
ripped me to shreds but
like just like you down
yeah and it was just like
you know what the next I'm
telling you man and this is what I'm saying
when you
have good support I'm
I walked in the next I
took school seriously from
then on in like I did not
everything was serious
because I was like I'm not going to be a loser
I and all that like some of
these quotes that I talk or
these motivational talks that
I like I'll get into a lot of it came from him
like because again like when you have good
people around
you and they really want to see you win
you have a great chance of
winning the opportunities there
you have a great chance as long as you want it
yep I didn't want to go out I didn't want to
be a loser
and then he talked about hockey
he was like yo like you're
so great at hockey but you're
not gonna have it like he
broke it down in a way where I
like yo life hit me you know
like it's like that life hit it
like that life-changing moment that shit hit
you
yep
you know what Landy I know I
have an arrogant face okay
people think I'm cocky and I
can't say I'm I might be cocky down there
put on the pit vipers where are they
I'm sorry as soon as you said
something the other day about having pit
vipers
I do have pit vipers this idea off
I have three pit vipers
it's just that the the one of
them the first ones I ever
bought my dog got a my dog's
got a fucking hold of them so I
I need I need to get them repaired
yeah that's uh
yeah that's no good okay you
can't you know the dogs wanted to
participate they wanted to go on
a mog spree and uh and
unfortunately dogs have a tough
time putting uh pit vipers on so
you know sometimes they get chewed up a little
bit
I'm a geek man I'm a geek
anyway
thank you Landy
thank you David Landy has a show today at
9 p.m. eastern standard time you
can go ahead and tune in if you'd like to go
ahead and learn
something um some say it's boring but some say
it's phenomenal
you can go ahead and tune in and see
where you stand with it 9 p.m.
eastern standard time
I won't be on there I'll be chilling working
out
okay it is sunny outside right now
I'm going to tan my balls
I might be on with Rob depending on if he has
a show
today he's probably sleeping
don't wake him up
check out Landy give Landy a follow
guys I want to thank you all for tuning in
today shout out to Leonidas
thank you to the $DOG Army for coming through
hopefully
you'll come through more often
shout out to everybody who supports me I
appreciate you I really do
I hope everybody fucking wins out here really
do
it's a great fucking industry
it is really great to build here
more people should be building here
build for the right reasons
get more people into crypto
it's a phenomenal place
we can all win together okay
and on that note as my friend Big Unk would
say have a great day
and an even better tomorrow
I'll see you next time I'll see you next time
I'll see you next time
[Music]